<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
					<channel>
						<title>AOM Career Services Search Results (Jobs)</title>
						<link>https://jobs.aom.org</link>
						<description>Latest AOM Career Services Jobs</description>
						<pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 02:57:51 Z</pubDate>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15749877/assistant-associate-professor-hospitality-professor-of-environmental-social-and-corporate-governan</link>

								<title>ASSISTANT/ASSOCIATE PROFESSOR Hospitality Professor of Environmental, Social, and Corporate Governan | Hilton College</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15749877/assistant-associate-professor-hospitality-professor-of-environmental-social-and-corporate-governan</guid>
								<description>Houston, Texas,  We welcome candidates whose experience in teaching, research, or community service has prepared them to contribute to our commitment to diversity and excellence. The University of Houston is an Affirmative Action/Equal Opportunity Employer.&#xa0; Minorities, women, veterans, and persons with disabilities are encouraged to apply.
 The Conrad N. Hilton College of Hotel and Restaurant Management  has an opening for an Assistant Professor with expertise in  Environmental, Social, and/or Corporate Governance .&#xa0; The University of Houston is a major, public, comprehensive research university situated in the fourth largest city in the United States.&#xa0; The College is one of the leading hospitality and tourism programs in the world.&#xa0; It is located in a world-class facility that contains extensive laboratory facilities, a library, convention space and a hotel.&#xa0; Qualifications

 This position requires an earned doctorate.
 Research must focus within the context of environment efforts, social, and/or corporate governance. This could include a focus on topics such as renewable energy, pollution, sustainability, equity, diversity, inclusion, sexual harassment, corporate social responsibility, and/or strategic management. &#xa0;It should be applicable to the hospitality industry.
 Candidates must have demonstrated the ability to publish in top-tier journals.
 Two years of teaching experience at the community college and/or university level preferred.
 Management experience within the hotel/tourism industry preferred.
 Appointment at the academic rank of an Associate professor may be considered for candidates with relevant experience, grant funding, and national/international reputation.

 Responsibilities

 Teach related courses at the undergraduate and graduate level
 Supervise doctoral students
 Publish within the top-tier hospitality and tourism journals
 Serve on College committees as assigned
 Attend College and University meetings and events
 Other duties as assigned by the administration

 The College is seeking to identify successful candidates with strong research and teaching skills.&#xa0; A candidate should identify their research and teaching areas in a letter of interest, curriculum vitae, and a copy of a recent publication if available.&#xa0; Applications and nominations for these positions will be accepted until the positions are filled.&#xa0; For information, please contact the search committee chair, Dr. Juan Madera at  jmmadera@central.uh.edu .
 &#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 10:50:05 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15749977/professor-of-the-practice-in-engineering-management</link>

								<title>Professor of the Practice in Engineering Management | Vanderbilt University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15749977/professor-of-the-practice-in-engineering-management</guid>
								<description>Nashville, Tennessee,  The Vanderbilt University School of Engineering (Department of General Engineering ? GE) is seeking applications for two full?time, Professor of the Practice (PoP) faculty positions with a target start date of Spring or Fall 2022. These are open rank appointments. Primary responsibilities are to teach three Applied Behavioral Science, and Organizational Behavior and Leadership courses per semester at the Department&#8217;s undergraduate and graduate Engineering Management programs. These are core courses for the Engineering Management minor ?the most popular minor in the School of Engineering? and the Master in Engineering Management program, and are very well attended by the students. Our undergraduate students are high performers with an interest in the intersection of technology, business, and innovation. Our graduate students are experienced industry professionals that aspire to lead teams in technology?based enterprises. The successful candidate is expected to advise undergraduate students in the interdisciplinary engineering major and mentor independent study and undergraduate research projects. Ideal qualifications include significant experience (10+ years) in industry (preferably in HR roles), prior teaching experience, and a Ph.D. in organizational behavior, corporate psychology, human resource management, or related field. Candidates with an understanding of the human resource aspects in engineering and technology organizations are preferred.</description>
								<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 16:42:42 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15817238/tenured-tenure-track-faculty-position-in-strategy</link>

								<title>Tenured/Tenure-track Faculty Position in Strategy | Universit&#xe9; Laval</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15817238/tenured-tenure-track-faculty-position-in-strategy</guid>
								<description>Qu&#xe9;bec, Quebec, Canada,  The Management Department at Universit&#xe9; Laval is currently seeking candidates for a tenure-track position in Strategy. Teaching and research interests should focus on strategy development and implementation processes (e.g., strategic decision making, managerial action, organizational resources and constraints).
 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;
 JOB DESCRIPTION

 Teaching and supervising undergraduate and graduate students, in-class and online.
 Research and publication in fields related to the position.
 Participation in educational and administrative activities of the Department and the Faculty.
 Participation in academic activities, off-campus and abroad, that contribute to the visibility of the University, and the Faculty.


 Ph. D. in Business Administration in Strategy or another relevant field. Doctoral students with significant progress towards their degree (i.e. ABD) will be considered.
 Demonstrated ability to conduct high quality scholarly work by research funding and/or relevant publications in peer-reviewed journals.
 Demonstrated ability to teach at both undergraduate and graduate levels, in-class and/or online.
 Ability to teach in French within the first three years of employment.
 Ability to teach in English would be an asset.
 Ability and interest in working in multidisciplinary teams with an active presence on campus.
 Professional Experience and recognition in strategy would be an asset.

 Persons interested in applying for the position are invited to submit, before February 13 th , 2022 and to the following address:  mng-recrutement@fsa.ulaval.ca , an application file that includes :

 a letter of intent in French,
 a detailed resum&#xe9;,
 a short description of the research program in French,
 two (2) recent and relevant publications.
 course evaluations for the last two years (if applicable),
 two (2) letters of reference.
 Salary in accordance with the current collective agreement at Universit&#xe9; Laval (https://www.rh.ulaval.ca/personnel-enseignant-et-de-recherche/professeurs/conventions-collectives)</description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 15:29:21 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15816937/harvard-university-china-public-policy-postdoctoral-fellowships</link>

								<title>Harvard University China Public Policy Postdoctoral Fellowships | HARVARD Kennedy School Ash Center for Democratic Governance and Innovation</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15816937/harvard-university-china-public-policy-postdoctoral-fellowships</guid>
								<description>Cambridge, Massachusetts,  The Ash Center for Democratic Governance and Innovation at the Harvard Kennedy School will offer one postdoctoral fellowship in the field of contemporary Chinese public policy to recent PhD degree recipients of exceptional promise. Application deadline is  January 5, 2022 (Wednesday) at 11:59PM EST.
 Eligibility
 Applicants must have received their PhD within five years of the start of the fellowship in a relevant social sciences discipline. Preference will be given to those working in the areas of contemporary domestic politics, political economy, business-government relations, state-society relations, and social/legal/economic development of China, particularly on issues related to urbanization, political/economic reform, energy/environment, social welfare, and civil society.
 Knowledge of Chinese is required, as well as the ability to work with original sources. Residence in the Cambridge area and participation in the activities of the Center throughout the academic year also required. It is expected that the successful applicant will give at least one research presentation during the fellowship period as well as participate in the Center&#8217;s publication program. Foreign nationals must be eligible for J-1 visa sponsorship. Those who are chosen to receive fellowships must have their degree conferral by June 1, 2022.
 Benefits
 Each fellowship will run for a period of up to two years. The recipient will receive an annual stipend of $65,000, health insurance, and dedicated workspace.
 How to Apply
 The next fellowship will begin August 1, 2022. To submit an application for the 2022-24 fellowship, please refer to http://ash.harvard.edu/china- public-policy-postdoctoral-fellowships . Email the completed application form, research proposal, current CV, scholarly writing samples and 2 letters of recommendation by  January 5, 2022 (Wednesday) at 11:59PM EST  to Laura_ma@hks.harvard.edu with &#8220;China Public Policy Postdoctoral Fellowship&#8221; in the SUBJECT line. Recommendation letters must be emailed directly by the recommender. All recommendation letters must be received for full consideration.
 Please note that we do not provide critique/feedback on unsuccessful applications.
 Further inquiries should be directed to Laura Ma, Associate Director for China Programs at the Ash Center at Laura_ma@hks.harvard.edu</description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 12:46:53 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15817299/associate-professor-of-public-health-policy-and-management</link>

								<title>Associate Professor of Public Health Policy and Management | New York University, School of Global Public Health</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15817299/associate-professor-of-public-health-policy-and-management</guid>
								<description>New York, New York,  The School of Global Public Health (GPH) at New York University seeks applications for Associate Professor (tenured/tenure track) within the Department of Public Health Policy and Management. We seek an energetic, innovative researcher and teacher who works collaboratively to join our growing faculty.&#xa0; Areas of interest could include:&#xa0; implementation science; public health management and financing; health information technology; health systems redesign and delivery; or global health systems and governance, particularly as they apply to non-communicable diseases, climate change, women&#8217;s health, and service delivery across nations.&#xa0;
 The Department of Public Health Policy and Management (PHPM) is home to a group of vibrant researchers from different disciplines including law, management, public administration, medicine and economics. PHPM has about 170 MPH students and several PhD and DrPH students, and teaches courses in the school&#8217;s undergraduate program. The department houses GPH&#8217;s growing Global Center for Implementation Science, headed by Dr. Donna Shelley. Applicants with an interest in implementation science are especially encouraged to apply. The candidate will be expected to teach departmental courses, serve on committees and mentor students, as well as maintaining an active and productive research agenda.
 GPH seeks candidates of exceptional potential and emerging scholarship who can contribute to the academic and research enterprise in NYC and throughout New York University&#8217;s key Global Network University (GNU) campuses and study-away sites (3 portal campuses and 12 global academic centers in Africa, South America, North America, China, Australia, Europe, and the Middle East).&#xa0; The unique GNU arrangement allows GPH faculty to establish training and degree programs and research efforts worldwide; offers faculty and students truly unique opportunities to engage in their research and study around the world and informs public health practice both locally and globally through the exchange of knowledge.
 GPH offers academic degrees at the undergraduate, masters and doctoral levels. The undergraduate program includes 13 joint majors where students study public health with other relevant subjects. The CEPH-accredited Master of Public Health degree allows students to obtain an MPH in one of nine concentrations, and the PhD in Public Health is offered in one of four areas of study &#8211; Biostatistics, Epidemiology, Social &#38; Behavioral Sciences, and Public Health Policy &#38; Management.&#xa0; In addition, a new school-wide, interdisciplinary DrPH degree launched in September 2021.
 Diversity &#38; Inclusion Statement: &#xa0;At NYU we are committed to inclusive excellence.&#xa0; Inclusion is foundational to scholarly excellence and critical to developing pathways to training for students traditionally underrepresented in the academy and/or particular disciplines. The diversity and inclusion statement offers each applicant the opportunity to highlight their past, present, and future contributions to creating inclusive excellence.&#xa0;&#xa0;
 We recognize that local contexts vary across departments and disciplines and that contributions to diversity and inclusion may take many forms.&#xa0; Efforts to cultivate inclusive excellence might include, for example, creating opportunities for students, faculty, and staff traditionally underrepresented in the U.S. academy and/or particular disciplines; public or primary school outreach (particularly to underserved communities); contributions to the diversity of thought and perspective; efforts to increase inclusion and equity at the university or in the local community; as well as one&#8217;s own life experience.
 Below are a few examples of contributions to inclusion that might be developed in a diversity &#38; inclusion statement.&#xa0; These are by no means exhaustive.&#xa0; Your statement might expand on how you have gone about:
 Fostering inclusion and building pathways in your discipline by
 ?&#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; Creating an inclusive and accessible classroom/course (including developing your skills for so doing)
 ?&#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; Working with campus organizations that support underrepresented, first-generation, differently-abled or non-traditional undergraduate or graduate students
 ?&#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; Developing discipline or area-specific pathways to majors for such students (e.g., Women in Science)
 ?&#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; Mentoring individual students, faculty or staff from diverse backgrounds
 ?&#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; Training international students or mentoring faculty from developing countries
 ?&#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; Working with your national scholarly organization on diversity, inclusion or equity issues, or
 Broadening the influence of your work for the public and enhancing underserved communities by
 ?&#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; Participating in K-12 classroom, museums, or other afterschool programming aimed at fostering general education, excitement, and possibility (particularly in underserved populations)
 ?&#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; Providing apprenticeships and internships for pre-college students
 ?&#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; Participating in prison education or other adult education programs that serve under-resourced populations
 ?&#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; Developing educational programming thru the media or social media
 ?&#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; Bringing results of research back to local or international communities
 ?&#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; Participating as a &#8216;public intellectual&#8217; on timely issues
 ?&#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; Engaging in community activities around education, social justice, equity, and inclusion.
 Qualifications


 Applicants must have an earned doctorate in business administration, health administration, health services research, health policy, sociology, organizational behavior, public health or other relevant disciplines. Applicants also must have a strong record of peer-reviewed publications and a track record of extramural funding for research as needed, commensurate with level of appointment.&#xa0;
 &#xa0;





 Application Instructions


 Applicants must submit:


 Cover letter addressing candidate&#8217;s qualifications for the position


 A statement of research and teaching interests


 A diversity and inclusion statement


 Curriculum vitae


 Three recent publications


 Name and contact information of three references&#xa0;


 &#xa0;
 Review of applications will begin November 30, 2021 and continue until the position is filled.
 For further information, please contact:&#xa0; Dr. Diana Silver, diana.silver@nyu.edu or Dr. Donna Shelly, donna.shelly@nyu.edu.
 &#xa0;





 Equal Employment Opportunity Statement


 For people in the EU, click here for information on your privacy rights under GDPR:&#xa0; www.nyu.edu/it/gdpr
 NYU is an Equal Opportunity Employer and is committed to a policy of equal treatment and opportunity in every aspect of its recruitment and hiring process without regard to age, alienage, caregiver status, childbirth, citizenship status, color, creed, disability, domestic violence victim status, ethnicity, familial status, gender and/or gender identity or expression, marital status, military status, national origin, parental status, partnership status, predisposing genetic characteristics, pregnancy, race, religion, reproductive health decision making, sex, sexual orientation, unemployment status, veteran status, or any other legally protected basis. Women, racial and ethnic minorities, persons of minority sexual orientation or gender identity, individuals with disabilities, and veterans are encouraged to apply for vacant positions at all levels.
 Sustainability Statement&#xa0;
 NYU aims to be among the greenest urban campuses in the country and carbon neutral by 2040. Learn more at&#xa0;nyu.edu/sustainability</description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 16:00:27 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15817319/corporate-sustainability-open-faculty-position</link>

								<title>Corporate Sustainability Open Faculty Position | University of California Santa Barbara</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15817319/corporate-sustainability-open-faculty-position</guid>
								<description>Santa Barbara, California,  Corporate Sustainability Open Faculty Position

 Position overview
 Position titles:



 Full or Associate Professor of Corporate Environmental Management




 Assistant Professor of Corporate Environmental Management




 Tenure Track Teaching Faculty in Corporate Environmental Management




 Tenured Teaching Faculty in Corporate Environmental Management



 Percent time:  100
 Anticipated start:  July 1, 2022
 Application Window
 Open date:  November 16th, 2021
 Next review date:   Thursday, Dec 16, 2021 at 11:59pm (Pacific Time) Apply by this date to ensure full consideration by the committee.
 Final date:  Thursday, Jun 30, 2022 at 11:59pm (Pacific Time) Applications will continue to be accepted until this date, but those received after the review date will only be considered if the position has not yet been filled.
 Position description


 The Bren School of Environmental Science &#38; Management ( www.bren.ucsb.edu ) invites applications for an open-rank faculty position in corporate sustainability. The position is open rank and may be in the University of California&#39;s Professor series or Teaching Professor in the UC&#39;s Lecturer with Security of Employment (LSOE) series. Professors and Teaching Professors are full Academic Senate positions, with teaching Professors carrying heavier teaching and less research responsibilities. Candidate qualifications should be commensurate with the series and rank. Evaluation of candidates for appointment in the Teaching Professor series will weigh potential contributions to teaching and leadership more heavily.
 The Bren School is a leader in developing cross-disciplinary solutions to environmental problems. The School&#39;s Corporate Environmental Management specialization prepares Master&#39;s students for careers helping companies achieve their business and environmental goals. The Bren School is a graduate school within UCSB that provides rigorous, multi-disciplinary training in environmental science and management to Master&#39;s and PhD students. The faculty are drawn from the natural sciences, social sciences, engineering, and management.
 The Bren School is open to candidates from business schools and from across the social sciences, including economics, political science, sociology, and psychology.
 The Bren School is especially interested in candidates who can contribute to the diversity and excellence of the academic community through research, teaching and service. At Bren, we recognize the intrinsic relationship between diversity and excellence in all our endeavors; we embrace open, inclusive, and equitable access to opportunities for learning and development as our obligation and goal. Our excellence can only be fully realized by faculty, students and staff who share our commitment to these principles. Successful candidates for faculty positions will demonstrate evidence of a commitment to equity and inclusion in their application materials, including the Statement describing contributions to diversity. This evidence can include:
 -Efforts to advance equitable access to education; -Public service that addresses the needs of California&#39;s diverse population; -Research that highlights inequalities; -Mentoring and advising students, particularly from underrepresented and underserved populations; -Creating effective strategies for the educational advancement of students in under-represented groups.



 School :  https://www.bren.ucsb.edu/

 Qualifications
 Basic qualifications   (required at time of application)

 Applicants must have completed all requirements for a PhD (or other terminal degree) except the dissertation at the time of application.


 Additional qualifications   (required at time of start)

 PhD or other terminal degree required by the time of hire.


 Preferred qualifications

 Candidates may teach and do research in areas such as strategy, management and organizations, organizational behavior, leadership, organizational theory and entrepreneurship.
 Ideal candidates will offer a combination of:
 -An accomplished research portfolio and/or a trajectory that includes significant contributions to understanding corporate sustainability. -Demonstrated or potential excellence in teaching business and corporate sustainability to professional Master&#39;s degree students. -Leadership for the School&#39;s Corporate Environmental Management programs. -Synergies with the School&#39;s research, teaching and extended communities in the pursuit of sustainable environmental solutions. -A demonstrated record of or potential contributions to diversity, equity, and inclusion.


 Application Requirements by Level

 Full Professor and Associate Professor

 Position title:  Full or Associate Professor of Corporate Environmental Management


 Applicants for a Full or Associate Professor Position must submit: 1) a cover letter, 2) curriculum vitae, 3) statements of research/professional activities and teaching, 4) statement describing contributions to diversity, 5) up to four selected writing samples, and 6) contact information for at least three references. Applicants for Full or Associate Professor may submit teaching evaluations if available.
 Individuals should submit their application at this level if they meet one of the following conditions: Current tenured professor; position equivalent to tenured professor or position (e.g. at an international university). Please note that this determination is only for application review purposes, not the ultimate appointment level of the finalist.

 Document requirements



 Curriculum Vitae - Your most recently updated C.V.




 Cover Letter




 Statement of Teaching




 Statement of Research and Professional Engagement




 Statement Describing Contributions to Diversity - Statement addressing past and/or potential contributions to diversity through research, teaching, and/or service.




 Writing Samples




 Teaching Evaluations if available (Optional)





 Reference requirements

 3-5 required (contact information only)


 References will only be contacted if candidate becomes a finalist.


 Apply link:   https://recruit.ap.ucsb.edu/JPF02066

 Assistant Professor

 Position title:  Assistant Professor of Corporate Environmental Management


 Applicants for an Assistant Professor Position must submit: 1) a cover letter, 2) curriculum vitae, 3) statements of research/professional activities and teaching, 4) statement describing contributions to diversity, 5) up to four selected writing samples, and 6) arrange for least three letters of reference to be submitted on their behalf via the UC Recruit website, ideally by the current review date. Applicants for Assistant Professor may submit teaching evaluations if available.
 Individuals should submit their application at this level if they meet one of the following conditions: Current or recent PhD candidate or graduate; current or recent postdoc; current assistant professor (including those who are &quot;senior&quot; assistant professors near tenure). Please note that this level determination is only for application review purposes, not the ultimate appointment level of the finalist.

 Document requirements



 Curriculum Vitae - Your most recently updated C.V.




 Cover Letter




 Statement of Teaching




 Statement of Research and Professional Engagement




 Statement Describing Contributions to Diversity - Statement addressing past and/or potential contributions to diversity through research, teaching, and/or service.




 Writing Samples




 Teaching Evaluations if available (Optional)





 Reference requirements

 3-5 letters of reference required


 Candidate must request letters from contacts in UC Recruit in order for the application to be considered complete.


 Apply link:   https://recruit.ap.ucsb.edu/JPF02066

 Lecturer PSOE

 Position title:  Tenure Track Teaching Faculty in Corporate Environmental Management


 Applicants for a Lecturer PSOE position must submit: 1) a cover letter, 2) curriculum vitae, 3) statements of research/professional activities and teaching, 4) statement describing contributions to diversity, 5) up to four selected writing samples, and 6) arrange for least three letters of reference to be submitted on their behalf via the UC Recruit website, ideally by the current review date. Applicants for Lecturer PSOE may submit teaching evaluations if available.
 Individuals should submit their application at this level if they meet one of the following conditions: Current or recent PhD candidate or graduate; current or recent postdoc; current assistant professor (including those who are &quot;senior&quot; assistant professors near tenure). Please note that this level determination is only for application review purposes, not the ultimate appointment level of the finalist.

 Document requirements



 Curriculum Vitae - Your most recently updated C.V.




 Cover Letter




 Statement of Teaching




 Statement of Research and Professional Engagement




 Statement Describing Contributions to Diversity - Statement addressing past and/or potential contributions to diversity through research, teaching, and/or service.




 Writing Samples




 Teaching Evaluations if available (Optional)





 Reference requirements

 3-5 letters of reference required


 Candidate must request letters from contacts in UC Recruit in order for the application to be considered complete.


 Apply link:   https://recruit.ap.ucsb.edu/JPF02066

 Lecturer SOE and Senior Lecturer SOE

 Position title:  Tenured Teaching Faculty in Corporate Environmental Management


 Applicants for a Lecturer SOE and Senior Lecturer SOE position must submit: 1) a cover letter, 2) curriculum vitae, 3) statements of research/professional activities and teaching, 4) statement describing contributions to diversity, 5) up to four selected writing samples, and 6) arrange for least three letters of reference to be submitted on their behalf via the UC Recruit website, ideally by the current review date. Applicants for Lecturer SOE and Senior Lecturer SOE may submit teaching evaluations if available.
 Individuals should submit their application at this level if they meet one of the following conditions: Current or recent PhD candidate or graduate; current or recent postdoc; current assistant professor (including those who are &quot;senior&quot; assistant professors near tenure). Please note that this level determination is only for application review purposes, not the ultimate appointment level of the finalist.

 Document requirements



 Curriculum Vitae - Your most recently updated C.V.




 Cover Letter




 Statement of Teaching




 Statement of Research and Professional Engagement




 Statement Describing Contributions to Diversity - Statement addressing past and/or potential contributions to diversity through research, teaching, and/or service.




 Writing Samples




 Teaching Evaluations if available (Optional)





 Reference requirements

 3-5 required (contact information only)


 References will only be contacted if candidate becomes a finalist.


 Apply link:   https://recruit.ap.ucsb.edu/JPF02066

 Help contact:   kellykeogh@ucsb.edu

 Campus Information


 The University of California is an Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action Employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.
 As a condition of employment, you will be required to comply with the University of California SARS-CoV-2 (COVID-19) Vaccination Program Policy  https://policy.ucop.edu/doc/5000695/SARS-CoV-2_Covid-19 . All Covered Individuals under the policy must provide proof of Full Vaccination or, if applicable, submit a request for Exception (based on Medical Exemption, Disability, and/or Religious Objection) or Deferral (based on pregnancy) no later than the applicable deadline. New University of California employees must (a) provide proof of receiving at least one dose of a COVID-19 Vaccine no later than 14 calendar days after their first date of employment and provide proof of Full Vaccination no later than eight weeks after their first date of employment; or (b) if applicable, submit a request for Exception or Deferral no later than 14 calendar days after their first date of employment. (Capitalized terms in this paragraph are defined in the policy.) Federal, state, or local public health directives may impose additional requirements.


 Job location
 Santa Barbara, CA

 Copyright &#xa9;2021 Jobelephant.com Inc. All rights reserved. Posted by the FREE value-added recruitment advertising agency     jeid-48ce2377ec2d6545b331d0260e4f8192</description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 16:11:02 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15805945/associate-professorship-in-social-entrepreneurship-and-innovation-100</link>

								<title>Associate Professorship in Social Entrepreneurship and Innovation (100%) | Universit&#xe4;t St.Gallen</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15805945/associate-professorship-in-social-entrepreneurship-and-innovation-100</guid>
								<description>St.Gallen, Switzerland,  &#xab;A place where knowledge is created&#xbb;
 As a leading business university we set global standards for research and teaching by promoting integrative thought, responsible action and an entrepreneurial spirit of innovation in business and society.
 &#xa0;
 Associate Professorship in Social Entrepreneurship and Innovation (100%)
 &#xa0;
 The University of St.Gallen and its School of Management are seeking candidates for an Associate Professorship in the field of Social Entrepreneurship and Innovation. The triple accredited (EQUIS, AACSB, AMBA) university offers a stimulating research environment with a large network, ranging from start-ups and small businesses to large firms, to engage in field studies.
 The new associate professor in the School of Management will become part of a dynamic team working at the intersection of social entrepreneurship, innovation, and sustainability. The position involves teaching in English (and preferably also in German) at all levels and in different programs and engaging in co-curricular activity with students. We are looking for a candidate with both an internationally recognised research track record in the leading entrepreneurship and management science journals, as well as excellent teaching skills.
 We seek candidates per August 1 st , 2022 or by mutual agreement.
 For further information, please contact Professor Dr. Reinhard Jung, Chairman of the Search Committee and Dean of the School of Management ( facultyposition@unisg.ch ).
 The application should include a cover letter (motivation for the position, description of teaching, research, and other academic activities), curriculum vitae, list of publications, identification of two publications that best represent your current research, and contact information for two professional references that we may contact if shortlisted for the position. Candidates should submit their application to the President of the University of St.Gallen, Professor Dr. Bernhard Ehrenzeller, online via&#xa0; www.unisg.ch/professorships &#xa0;at the latest by December 31 th &#xa0;2021.
 The University of St.Gallen is strongly committed to promoting equal opportunities and diversity. We specifically encourage women and applicants with backgrounds underrepresented among our current senior faculty to apply.</description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 05:15:20 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15808030/associate-dean-academic-odette-school-of-business</link>

								<title>Associate Dean, Academic - Odette School of Business | University of Windsor</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15808030/associate-dean-academic-odette-school-of-business</guid>
								<description>Windsor, Ontario, Canada,  The University of Windsor&#8217;s Odette School of Business invites applications for the position of Associate Dean, Academic, commencing July 1, 2022. This is a five-year renewable term. This position is subject to final budgetary approval. Located at one of Canada&#8217;s major international intersections, the University of Windsor, considered to be Canada&#8217;s most personal comprehensive university, plays a leading role in the future of the region and the Province of Ontario. The Odette School of Business takes a balanced approach to research and teaching. The School offers varied degrees in business including an undergraduate Bachelor of Commerce Degree, a full-time MBA; an MBA for managers and professionals; an MBA-PAS (Professional Accounting Specialization); and a Master of Management in four subdisciplines (Data Analytics, Accounting and Finance, Human Resources, and Supply Chain Management). Approximately 1200 full-time, and 400 Master&#8217;s-level students study at Odette. The Business School has strong contacts with business and other academic institutions. The School has recently completed an expansion strategy and has approximately 65 full-time faculty positions. The School has been AACSB accredited since 2015. For further information about the Odette School of Business visit our website at http://www.uwindsor.ca/business. Reporting to the Dean of the Odette School of Business, the Associate Dean, Academic is responsible for the leadership and ongoing operations of all School activities related to faculty members and specific discipline areas within the School. The incumbent will work collaboratively and collegially with the decanal/executive team and is responsible for the development and implementation of processes to assist in faculty member development, for managing the maintenance of the School&#8217;s AACSB accreditation, and contributing to the implementation and refinement of the School&#8217;s strategic plan. This will be accomplished by managing and/or consulting in the following activities: &#8226; Create and/or facilitate the development of documentation required by various internal and external accrediting agencies, engaging others in the School as required to fulfill these needs; &#8226; Conduct, as requested by the Dean, faculty performance reviews and tenure determinations. Serve, on behalf of the Dean, as Chair of the faculty Renewal, Promotion and Tenure Committee; &#8226; Head, on behalf of the Dean, the development of initiatives to support the School strategy in conjunction with Area Chairs and Program Directors; &#8226; Take an active role in implementing and advancing the School&#8217;s Equity, Diversity, Inclusion, and Indigenization (EDII) Strategy &#8226; In cooperation with the Odette Research Leadership Chair (or Associate Dean, Research) and the Dean, ensure the research strategies of the School and of individual Areas and faculty members are in place and effective; &#8226; Implement and lead, under direction from the Dean, all non-program-related parts of the School&#8217;s strategy implementation and related actions; &#8226; Initiate, administer and/or coordinate, in collaboration with the Dean and Faculty Council, all OSB academic policies, procedures, and processes as they affect faculty members; &#8226; Be responsible for all non-program, non-finance information and its maintenance via databases or other records; &#8226; In consultation with the Dean, oversee relevant processes for faculty complaints and grievances and their proper resolution; &#8226; Initiate and ensure delivery of faculty career development and advice-giving processes; &#8226; Ensure that appropriate School guidelines for faculty research, teaching, and service performance are in place, overseeing the processes that engage the necessary input and approvals; &#8226; Represent OSB with various University groups, liaising with University officials as requested by the Dean; www.uwindsor.ca/facultypositions &#8226; When requested by the Dean, initiate, administer and/or coordinate new faculty recruitment and appointment processes to ensure they are run in equitable, efficient and effective ways; &#8226; In partnership with the Associate Dean, Programs, initiate, administer and/or coordinate new faculty orientations; &#8226; Represent the Dean and the School from time to time with various constituencies, especially with business leaders, alumni, and senior University Administrators; &#8226; Complete special projects and tasks as assigned by the Dean; and &#8226; Attend meetings on behalf of the Dean, when appropriate. Candidate profile: The ideal candidate holds a Ph.D. degree in business (or a related discipline), has an established track record as an academic administrator as an Associate Dean/Program Director/Discipline (Department) Chair or brings a distinguished academic reputation and/or an impressive track record in research, teaching and service suitable for a senior administrative position. The successful candidate will have the ability to work well with Area Chairs, Program Directors, and individual faculty in implementing the School&#8217;s mission and strategy with the various academic disciplines and individual faculty members. The candidate should show a record of AACSB involvement. The successful candidate must possess a demonstrated track record of working in a collegial manner with the decanal team, faculty, students, and staff. Upon appointment as Associate Dean, Academic, the candidate will be appointable as Associate or Full Professor with tenure and will have a reduced teaching load for the duration of their administrative term(s). Application Requirements: &#8226; a letter of application, including a statement of citizenship/immigration status; &#8226; a detailed and current curriculum vitae; &#8226; a teaching dossier or portfolio demonstrating potential for or evidence of teaching effectiveness and excellence that will include sample course syllabi/outlines, teaching evaluations, and a statement of teaching philosophy and interests (resources and templates for completing a teaching dossier can be found at https://www.uwindsor.ca/ctl/502/teaching-dossiers; and &#8226; three (3) current letters of reference forwarded directly by the referees to the Dean at the address or email listed below. The references should speak directly to the applicant&#8217;s ability to successfully fulfill the position profile. Only those applicants selected for interview will be contacted. The short-listed candidates may be invited to provide further information in support of their applications. To ensure full consideration, complete an online application (http://www.uwindsor.ca/faculty/recruitment/faculty-postings) found on the job advertisement by the deadline date of January 17, 2022. Applications may be considered after the deadline date; however, acceptance of late submissions is at the discretion of the appointments committee. Questions, Nominations, Applications, and Reference Letters to be sent to: Dr. Mitchell W. Fields, Dean, Odette School of Business, University of Windsor, 401 Sunset Avenue, Windsor, Ontario, Canada N9B 3P4 Phone: 519-253-3000 Ext. 3091; Email: aholiga@uwindsor.ca
 The University of Windsor is a comprehensive research and teaching institution with more than 16,000 students. We are a welcoming community committed to equity, diversity, inclusion, and accessibility in our teaching, learning, and work environments. In pursuit of the University&#39;s Employment Equity Plan, members from the designated groups (women, Indigenous/Aboriginal (First Nations, Metis, Inuit) persons, racialized persons/visible minorities, persons with disabilities, and persons of a minority sexual orientation and/or gender identity) are encouraged to apply and to self-identify. If you need an accommodation for any part of the application and hiring process, please notify the Faculty Recruitment Coordinator (recruit@uwindsor.ca). Should you require further information on accommodation, please visit the website of the Office of Human Rights, Equity &#38; Accessibility (http://www.uwindsor.ca/ohrea). All qualified candidates are encouraged to apply; however, Canadians and permanent residents will be given priority.</description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 09:13:07 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15806637/associate-professorship-in-social-entrepreneurship-and-innovation-100</link>

								<title>Associate Professorship in Social Entrepreneurship and Innovation (100%) | Universit&#xe4;t St.Gallen</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15806637/associate-professorship-in-social-entrepreneurship-and-innovation-100</guid>
								<description>St.Gallen, Switzerland,  &#xab;A place where knowledge is created&#xbb;
 As a leading business university we set global standards for research and teaching by promoting integrative thought, responsible action and an entrepreneurial spirit of innovation in business and society.
 &#xa0;
 Associate Professorship in Social Entrepreneurship and Innovation (100%)
 &#xa0;
 The University of St.Gallen and its School of Management are seeking candidates for an Associate Professorship in the field of Social Entrepreneurship and Innovation. The triple accredited (EQUIS, AACSB, AMBA) university offers a stimulating research environment with a large network, ranging from start-ups and small businesses to large firms, to engage in field studies.
 The new associate professor in the School of Management will become part of a dynamic team working at the intersection of social entrepreneurship, innovation, and sustainability. The position involves teaching in English (and preferably also in German) at all levels and in different programs and engaging in co-curricular activity with students. We are looking for a candidate with both an internationally recognised research track record in the leading entrepreneurship and management science journals, as well as excellent teaching skills.
 We seek candidates per August 1 st , 2022 or by mutual agreement.
 For further information, please contact Professor Dr. Reinhard Jung, Chairman of the Search Committee and Dean of the School of Management ( facultyposition@unisg.ch ).
 The application should include a cover letter (motivation for the position, description of teaching, research, and other academic activities), curriculum vitae, list of publications, identification of two publications that best represent your current research, and contact information for two professional references that we may contact if shortlisted for the position. Candidates should submit their application to the President of the University of St.Gallen, Professor Dr. Bernhard Ehrenzeller, online via&#xa0; www.unisg.ch/professorships &#xa0;at the latest by December 31 th &#xa0;2021.
 The University of St.Gallen is strongly committed to promoting equal opportunities and diversity. We specifically encourage women and applicants with backgrounds underrepresented among our current senior faculty to apply.</description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 05:23:35 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15798642/dean-andre-b-lacy-school-of-business</link>

								<title>Dean, Andre B. Lacy School of Business | Butler University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15798642/dean-andre-b-lacy-school-of-business</guid>
								<description>Indianapolis, Indiana,  Dean, Andre B. Lacy School of Business
 Butler University invites nominations and applications for the position of Dean of the Andre B. Lacy School of Business. Butler seeks a collaborative, creative, energetic, entrepreneurial, experienced, and inspiring leader who will not only serve as the chief academic and administrative officer for the school, but also will be outward-looking and visionary in leading the school to new levels of success. The Dean of the Andre B. Lacy School of Business reports to the Provost. Programs in the Lacy School of Business are accredited by the Association to Advance Collegiate Schools of Business (AACSB).
 Located in Indianapolis, Indiana, Butler University is a nationally recognized university with six academic colleges: Arts, Business, Communication, Education, Liberal Arts and Sciences, and Pharmacy and Health Sciences. Butler is known for providing students with small classes, opportunities to engage directly with faculty, and experiential education through internships, research with faculty mentors, study abroad, service-learning opportunities such as classroom placements for education students and healthcare site placements for pharmacy students, as well as numerous artistic performances. These opportunities give students the knowledge and skills they need to excel after college &#8211; both in the workforce and in life. Butler students have had significant success after graduation, as demonstrated by the University&#8217;s 97 percent placement rate within 12 months of graduation.
 For the fourth consecutive year, Butler is ranked as the top regional university in the Midwest by  U.S. News &#38; World Report . Additionally, Butler is ranked No. 1 among Midwest Regional Universities for innovation, undergraduate teaching, and the Best College for Veterans. Butler received national rankings for first-year experience (No. 16), and study abroad opportunities (No. 25).
 The Dean of the Lacy School of Business will have the opportunity to inspire, lead, and empower a community of strong faculty. In addition, the Dean will have the opportunity to develop and enhance the Lacy Schools modern academic programs and experiences for the student body. The Dean reports directly to the Provost, oversees a $11 million-dollar budget, and is responsible for all administrative and academic units of the School.&#xa0; Alongside the school&#8217;s leadership, 53 full-time faculty, 26 part-time faculty, work in a highly collegial and friendly environment to provide a stellar academic experience for students. The Lacy School is home to 1,099 undergraduate students pursuing degrees in  Accounting ,   Applied Business Technology (ABT) ,  Entrepreneurship &#38; Innovation ,  Economics ,  Finance ,  International Business ,  Marketing ,  Risk Management &#38; Insurance   and 234 graduate students who pursue degrees in  Accounting ,  Business Administration ,  Management , and  Risk and Insurance .&#xa0; The Lacy School of Business also hosts the  Butler&#8217;s Old National Bank Center for Business Excellence ,  Central Indiana Small Business Development Center , and  Innovation Lab .
 The successful candidate for this position has a record of distinguished academic leadership, research and teaching and/or strong leadership experience in industry. Applicants should have experience in business and management in an academic and/or professional environment including planning, budgeting, team building, problem solving and project management. Candidates should have a proven record of professional accomplishments and effective leadership, and have demonstrated the ability to foster a climate where learning and discovery flourish.
 To access the full position profile, please see:  https://assets.storbecksearch.com/files/resources/butler-businessdean-pd.pdf .
 Review of application materials will begin immediately and will continue until the position is filled. Application materials will consist of a letter of interest, which among other areas should address areas of leadership and diversity, equity, and inclusion; curriculum vitae, and the names of five professional references. Nominations, inquiries, and expressions of interest should be forwarded in confidence to:
 Steve Leo, Managing Director
 Jeffrey Alston EDD, Senior Associate
 ButlerBusinessDean@storbecksearch.com
 Butler University is an equal opportunity employer. We celebrate diversity and are committed to creating an inclusive and equitable environment for all employees. We welcome applications from all individuals, regardless of age, gender, gender identity, sex, race, religion, color, disability, protected veteran status, sexual orientation, national origin, or any other legally protected category.</description>
								<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 15:40:47 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15798236/tenure-track-position-organizational-behaviour-human-resource-management</link>

								<title>Tenure-Track Position &#8211; Organizational Behaviour/Human Resource Management | Wilfrid Laurier University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15798236/tenure-track-position-organizational-behaviour-human-resource-management</guid>
								<description>Waterloo, Ontario, Canada,  Tenure-Track Position &#8211; Organizational Behaviour/Human Resource Management
 &#xa0;
 The Lazaridis School of Business &#38; Economics (Lazaridis School) at Wilfrid Laurier University invites applications for two tenure-track faculty positions, one at the Assistant Professor level, and the second at the Assistant or Associate Professor level in the OB/HRM area, commencing  July 1, 2022 . Candidates with an established research record of publications in top journals will be preferred. For at least one of these positions, research expertise in diversity in organizations will be considered an asset. These positions are subject to budgetary approval.
 &#xa0;
 Qualifications for the position at the rank of Assistant Professor include a Ph.D. or completion of a Ph.D. within one year of employment start date with an emphasis in Organizational Behaviour, Human Resources or related field.
 &#xa0;
 Successful candidates for the position at the rank of Assistant Professor must have:

 Demonstrated exceptional research potential,
 Demonstrated ability (a) to publish in top-tier business journals and (b) to maintain a highly productive research agenda,
 Ability to effectively teach courses at the undergraduate and research-based graduate (MSc and Ph.D.) levels,
 Demonstrated ability to communicate the relevance of their research to a business audience,
 Ability and interest to teach at the MBA level will be considered an asset.

 &#xa0;
 Qualifications for the position at the rank of Associate Professor include a Ph.D. with an emphasis in Organizational Behaviour, Human Resources or related field.
 &#xa0;
 Successful candidates for the position at the rank of Associate Professor must have:

 Demonstrated exceptional research potential,
 Track record of publishing in top-tier business journals and an established research program for ongoing research productivity,
 Evidence for teaching excellence at the undergraduate and graduate (MSc and Ph.D.) levels,
 Track record of successfully developing graduate students,
 Demonstrated ability to communicate the relevance of their research to a business audience,
 Ability and interest to teach at the MBA level will be considered an asset.

 &#xa0;
 The Lazaridis School of Business &#38; Economics has over 150 full-time faculty and more than 6000 undergraduate and graduate students on campuses in Waterloo and Brantford, and a location in Toronto, Ontario. With a mission to achieve excellence in management education, the school offers undergraduate and graduate degrees, including Honours BBA, MBA, MFin, MMA and PhD. Laurier&#8217;s undergraduate and graduate business programs are AACSB accredited. For more information, please visit  http://www.wlu.ca/lazaridisschool .
 &#xa0;
 Waterloo, Ontario is a highly innovative and dynamic region. It is the home to a number of leading high technology firms, insurance companies and educational/research institutions (e.g. University of Waterloo, the Balsillie School of International Affairs and the Perimeter Institute for Theoretical Physics).
 The Lazaridis School of Business &#38; Economics is also home to the Lazaridis Institute, which helps Canadian technology companies reach their next level of growth through world-class programs; leading-edge research in innovation, management and disruption in the tech ecosystem; and the connection of international research, best practices in global scaling, and curriculum.  http://www.lazaridisinstitute.ca
 &#xa0;
 Applications must include:

   A letter of application,
   A curriculum vitae,
   A teaching statement that includes a brief summary regarding teaching experience and effectiveness (including teaching evaluations),
   A summary of research objectives; best/selected research article(s),
   The names and emails of at least three academic referees.

 &#xa0;
 Only complete applications will be considered.&#xa0; All applications must include the Position Number 2022-01 and should be addressed to:
 &#xa0;
 Dr. Sapna Isotupa
 Associate Dean of Business: Faculty Development &#38; Research
 Lazaridis School of Business &#38; Economics
 Wilfrid Laurier University
 Waterloo, Ontario, N2L 3C5
 Email:  OBPTAC@wlu.ca
 &#xa0;
 Electronic applications should quote Position Number 2022-01.
 &#xa0;
 Deadline for applications is  December 17, 2021.
 &#xa0;
 Wilfrid Laurier University is committed to equity and values diversity. Laurier is committed to increasing the diversity of faculty and staff and welcomes applicants from qualified members of the equity-deserving groups. Indigenous candidates who would like to learn more about equity and inclusive programming at Laurier are welcome to contact the Office of Indigenous Initiatives at indigenous@wlu.ca. Candidates from other equity-deserving groups who would like to learn more about equity and inclusive programming at Laurier are welcomed to contact Equity and Accessibility at  equity@wlu.ca .&#xa0;
 &#xa0;
 All qualified candidates are encouraged to apply; however, as per Canadian immigration laws, Canadians and permanent residents will be given priority. To comply with the Government of Canada&#8217;s reporting requirements, the University is obligated to gather information about applicants&#8217; status as either Permanent Residents of Canada or Canadian citizens. Applicants need not identify their country of origin or current citizenships, however, all applicants must include one of the following statements in their cover letter:
 &#xa0;
 Yes, I am a current citizen or permanent resident of Canada;
 No, I am not a current citizen or permanent resident of Canada
 &#xa0;
 Members of the designated groups must self-identify to be considered for employment equity. Candidates should self-identify, in confidence, to Michael Lisetto-Smith, Senior Administrative Officer ( mlisettosmith@wlu.ca ). Further information on the equity policy can be found at  https://www.wlu.ca/about/governance/assets/resources/8.4-employment-equity.html .
 &#xa0;
 Applicants are encouraged to address any career interruptions or special circumstances that may have affected their record of research and teaching, in accordance with SSHRC and NSERC definitions and guidelines. To obtain a copy of this job description in an accessible format, please contact Justine MacNeil ( jumacneil@wlu.ca ).
 &#xa0;
 The Lazaridis School of Business &#38; Economics wishes to thank all applicants for their interest. All nominations and applications shall be reviewed and considered under a set of criteria established by the Search Committee and a short list of candidates shall be interviewed. Only those applicants selected for the short list will be contacted.
 &#xa0;
 Wilfrid Laurier University endeavors to fill positions with qualified candidates who have a combination of education, experience, skills and abilities to successfully perform the duties of the position while demonstrating Laurier&#39;s Employee Success Factors.
 &#xa0;
 Equity, diversity and creating a culture of inclusion are part of Laurier&#8217;s core values and central to the Laurier Strategy. Laurier is committed to increasing the diversity of faculty and staff and welcomes applications from candidates who identify as Indigenous, racialized, having disabilities, and from persons of any minority sexual and gender identities. Indigenous candidates who would like to learn more about equity and inclusive programing at Laurier are welcomed to contact the Office of Indigenous Initiatives. Candidates from other equity deserving groups who would like to learn more about equity and inclusive programing at Laurier are welcomed to contact Equity &#38; Accessibility. We have strived to make our application process accessible, however if you require any assistance applying for a position or would like this job posting in an alternative format, please contact Human Resources. Contact information can be found at careers.wlu.ca/content/How-to-Apply-/
 &#xa0;
 Should you be interested in learning more about this opportunity, please visit www.wlu.ca/careers for additional information and the online application system. All applications must be submitted online. Please note, a CV and letter of introduction will be required in electronic form.
 &#xa0;
 All Laurier employees and students are required to comply with the University&#8217;s Covid-19 mandatory vaccination policy. Prior to attending Laurier&#8217;s campuses in-person, you must provide proof of your vaccination status. If you are not fully vaccinated and do not have an approved exemption based on medical/disability or religious beliefs/creed grounds, you will be expected to receive your second dose of the vaccine by no later than October 8, 2021. Prior to becoming fully vaccinated, you will be required to participate in and comply with the University&#8217;s rapid testing program and follow all recommended additional health and safety protocols. Details about the mandatory vaccination requirements can be found on Laurier&#8217;s website at https://www.wlu.ca/news/spotlights/2021/aug/laurier-to-require-proof-of-vaccination-next-steps-for-students-and-employees.html&#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:44:17 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15798080/associate-professor-or-assistant-professor-tenure-track-of-microeconomics</link>

								<title>Associate Professor or Assistant Professor (Tenure Track) of Microeconomics | Universit&#xe4;t St.Gallen</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15798080/associate-professor-or-assistant-professor-tenure-track-of-microeconomics</guid>
								<description>St.Gallen, Switzerland,  &#xab;A place where knowledge is created&#xbb;
 As a leading business university we set global standards for research and teaching by promoting integrative thought, responsible action and an entrepreneurial spirit of innovation in business and society.
 Associate Professor or Assistant Professor (Tenure Track) of Microeconomics
 &#xa0;
 The University of St.Gallen and its School of Economics and Political Science are inviting applications for an Associate Professorship or an Assistant Professorship (Tenure Track) in the field of Microeconomics. Candidates with research interests in decision theory, applied microeconomic theory or the economics of digitization are particularly encouraged to apply. Candidates should have (or aspire to establish) a track record of internationally recognized research in leading general interest or field journals. Candidates further should have excellent teaching skills in microeconomics and the willingness to teach at all levels.
 &#xa0;
 We seek to fill the position per August 1 st , 2022 or by mutual agreement.
 For further information, please contact Professor Dr. Reto Foellmi, Chair of the Appointments Committee ( facultyposition@unisg.ch ).
 &#xa0;
 The application should include a cover letter (selection of relevant position, motivation to apply for the position, description of teaching, research, and other academic activities), curriculum vitae, list of publications, identification of two publications that best represent your current research, and contact information for two professional references that we may contact if shortlisted for the position. Candidates should submit their application to the President of the University of St.Gallen, Professor Dr. Bernhard Ehrenzeller online via&#xa0; www.unisg.ch/professorships &#xa0;at the latest by December 31 th &#xa0;2021.
 &#xa0;
 The University of St.Gallen is strongly committed to promoting equal opportunities and diversity. We specifically encourage women and applicants with backgrounds underrepresented among our current senior faculty to apply.</description>
								<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 09:46:24 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15792520/emerging-business-operations-strategy-manager</link>

								<title>Emerging Business Operations &#38; Strategy Manager | Meta Platforms, Inc. (Meta), formerly known as Facebook Inc.</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15792520/emerging-business-operations-strategy-manager</guid>
								<description>Menlo Park, California,  Meta Platforms, Inc. (Meta), formerly known as Facebook Inc., currently has an opening in Menlo Park, CA.&#xa0; The following&#xa0; Emerging Business Operations &#38; Strategy Manager &#xa0;position: Manage cross-functional infrastructure information technology programs in a matrix organization covering a range of areas. (138714)
 &#xa0;
 For full information and to apply online, visit us at the Facebook Careers page www.facebookcareers.com or navigate to our careers site on the Facebook About page about.facebook.com&#xa0;and click on Careers.
 &#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 13:35:27 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15793023/chief-of-staff</link>

								<title>Chief of Staff | CalOptima</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15793023/chief-of-staff</guid>
								<description>Orange, California,  Chief of Staff
 Job Description Department(s):  Executive Office Reports to:  Chief Executive Officer (CEO) FLSA Status:  Exempt Salary Grade:  U - $226,000 - $338,000 Job Summary As a member of the executive team, the Chief of Staff creates a shared sense of purpose to achieve an aligned vision executed through CalOptima&#39;s strategic plan and Chief Executive Officer (CEO) initiatives. Through executive leaders and directors, orchestrates the cross-collaborative development, implementation, and improvement of organizational programs and initiatives as assigned by the CEO. This position is a key leader within the health plan and has the responsibility and accountability to lead the areas assigned to next-level capabilities and operational efficiencies consistent with the strategic plan, goals, and objectives for CalOptima. The incumbent will anticipate, continuously improve, communicate, and leverage resources. The COS will balance achieving set accountabilities with constraints of limited resources. When directed, the incumbent will act as a liaison of the CEO with departments such as Information Services, Operations, Program Implementation, Provider Network Operations, Human Resources, Communications, Community Relations, Strategic Development and the executives and directors who have oversight of these departments. The Chief of Staff (COS) acts as advisor to the CEO and will support the CEO in the development and implementation of policy objectives, strategic planning, and activities involving internal stakeholders. Under the CEO&#39;s general guidance, the COS focuses on internal systems and is responsible for project management support for all high-priority operations, helping the CEO to prioritize time and resources according to organizational need while ensuring such priorities are communicated, and departments have the resources to meet assigned goals. While the CEO maintains Executive Leader Team supervision, the COS liaises with leadership and broader staff to advance work and facilitate processes and lead special initiatives and projects as assigned. Additionally, the Chief of Staff supports company&#39;s engagement and partners with agency leadership to develop communication strategies. For assigned programs, projects, and initiatives, the incumbent communicates crystal clear expectations of results, defines roles and responsibilities, assesses and diagnoses issues of accountability, clearly defines, communicates, and monitors individual and workgroup ownership and accountability, identifies and addresses obstacles, creates a sense of urgency when needed, provides CEO with progress reports, conducts after action reviews to ensure continuous improvement, and recommends new approaches to increase capabilities and efficiencies. Position Responsibilities:

 Supports the CEO&#39;s organizational priorities ensuring timelines and work plans are aligned and supporting his or her relationship with direct reports.
 Communicates consistent messaging and implementation of CEO&#39;s vision and priorities to achieve desired results.
 Works with leaders to develop key organizational metrics, or dashboard, to provide regular reports and findings to the CEO on the performance of such activities.
 Prepares communications, announcements, project plans, or similar documents for the CEO.
 Writes, edits, and reviews Board agendas and staff reports. Attends and participates in Board and Committee Meetings.
 Executes assigned organizational functions, aligns work activities to short- and long-term strategic objectives, balances resources, and supports organizational processes.
 Prepares leaders for change and internal collaboration related to CEO driven priorities.
 Provides transparent and constructive feedback and facilitates respectful conflict resolution within cross collaborative workgroups.
 Ensures tight operations across the office of the CEO and the broader organization by finding value-added solutions to gaps and problems.
 Provides thought partnership with colleagues and may lead organizational retreats and regularly occurring meetings including planning, preparation, and participation.
 Conducts follow-up and interfaces with staff to support CalOptima&#39;s responsiveness.
 With guidance from the CEO, provides support to senior-level staff responsible for the major functional areas of the organization.
 Coordinates and facilitates communication between departments and staff to ensure cross collaboration and optimal use of resources; implementation and alignment with the organization&#39;s strategic plan; integration of operations with program issues and fiscal needs; standardized protocols and practices; to enhance overall organizational communication to ensure clarify of direction and administrative effectiveness.
 In collaboration with the CEO, creates strategic communication and analytical documents.
 Plans and/or facilitates various organizational-level planning and decision-making bodies, including the support of the CalOptima&#39;s Executive Team. Provides input on the development, enhancement, and support of other meeting structures.
 Tracks and advises the CEO on progress throughout the duration of assigned projects.
 Communicates, plans, and provides operational considerations to the CEO and colleagues in the organization.
 Other projects and duties as assigned.

 Possesses the Ability To:

 Support the CEO and his/her vision for the organization and members.
 Maintain executive level confidentiality.
 Provide strategic thought partnership to the CEO.
 Keep perspective, exercise diplomacy, and a sense of resiliency during organizational transition.
 Establish and maintain effective, collaborative working relationships with CalOptima leaders and, staff and as directed with Board members.
 Demonstrate a track record and leadership in building organizational and staff capacity, developing a strong workforce and culture of accountability, and developing processes that ensure that the organization runs smoothly and efficiently in support of the Mission.
 Collaboratively work with the CEO to foster a healthy organizational culture, encourage collaboration and teamwork, and inspire and motivate staff with a mission-driven focus and modeling of high ethics and work practices. Promote teamwork and integration within and across the organization.
 Think strategically and analytically, incorporating new information and trends into organizational planning and program implementation to guide and inform the CEO&#39;s strategic direction and operational plans of the organization.
 Effectively plan, facilitate, contribute to, and represent the organization in meetings.
 Demonstrate cultural awareness and sensitivity in a variety of contexts.
 Communicate clearly and effectively, orally and in writing, to staff, key stakeholders, partners, the Board members, and the public, including the ability to write and edit reports and other written communications, and develop and deliver clear and compelling oral presentations.
 Define and address highly complex problems and issues requiring the analysis of multiple variables or situations; collect, synthesize, and analyze information; consider alternatives; and draw valid conclusions.
 Adapt, with minimal or no advance notice, to changes in operations, work assignments, procedures or requests from the CEO for the Board of Directors and Board Ad-hoc committees.
 Develop a wide variety of near and long-term strategic plans in support of the vision of the CEO.
 Exercise sound judgment within broadly defined practices and procedures to create and select appropriate strategies and make and carry out effective decisions at the direction of the CEO.

 Experience &#38; Education:

 Bachelor&#39;s degree in business or public administration, public health, public policy, social services, or related field is required.
 7 years of related experience supporting senior executives, preferably in the healthcare industry or a Managed Care environment, including at least four years of executive-level program administration, cross-functional operational planning, or strategy management experience is required.

 Preferred Qualifications:

 Master&#39;s degree in business or public administration is preferred.
 Experience across a variety of sectors, including government, non-profit, and for-profit organizations is preferred.

 Knowledge of:

 Strategic, operational, project planning and management principles and methodologies of a Medicaid health plan.
 Leadership principles of public administration and administrative analysis of a Medicaid health plan.
 General business principles and practices applicable to government agencies, such as quality improvement strategies, financial analysis, resource allocation, strategic planning.
 General program planning, development, and evaluation methodologies, including Results Based Accountability (RBA) and metrics development.
 Principles and practices of organizational development, performance management, and supervision, including workforce planning and resource allocation.
 State and Federal Guidelines related to Health Plans.
 Proficiency in Microsoft Office Suite, Office 365 preferred.

 CalOptima is an equal employment opportunity employer and makes all employment decisions on the basis of merit. CalOptima wants to have qualified employees in every job position. CalOptima prohibits unlawful discrimination against any employee, or applicant for employment, based on race, religion/religious creed, color, national origin, ancestry, mental or physical disability, medical condition, genetic information, marital status, sex, sex stereotype, gender, gender identity, gender expression, transitioning status, age, sexual orientation, immigration status, military status as a disabled veteran, or veteran of the Vietnam era, or any other consideration made unlawful by federal, state, or local laws. CalOptima also prohibits unlawful discrimination based on the perception that anyone has any of those characteristics or is associated with a person who has, or is perceived as having, any of those characteristics.   If you are a qualified individual with a disability or a disabled veteran, you may request a reasonable accommodation if you are unable or limited in your ability to access job openings or apply for a job on this site as a result of your disability. You can request reasonable accommodations by contacting Human Resources Disability Management at 657-900-1134. Job Location:  Orange, California Position Type:   To apply, visit  https://jobs.silkroad.com/CalOptima/Careers/jobs/3533 Copyright &#xa9;2021 Jobelephant.com Inc. All rights reserved. Posted by the FREE value-added recruitment advertising agency     jeid-979d67cbdbda61488019d506bebf703c</description>
								<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 20:07:27 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15792431/multiple-openings-for-meta-platforms-inc-f-k-a-facebook-inc</link>

								<title>Multiple Openings for Meta Platforms, Inc. (f/k/a Facebook, Inc.) | Meta Platforms, Inc. (f/k/a Facebook, Inc.)</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15792431/multiple-openings-for-meta-platforms-inc-f-k-a-facebook-inc</guid>
								<description>Austin, Texas,  Meta Platforms, Inc. (Meta), formerly known as Facebook Inc., currently has the following openings in Austin, TX.&#xa0; The following&#xa0; Business Integrity Associate &#xa0;position: Become a subject matter expert in workflows spanning a variety of business integrity disciplines (policy creation &#38; enforcement, content review, process optimization, spam research &#38; mitigation, advertiser experience, vendor management, measurement &#38; reporting) in order to effectively advocate for operational excellence of those workflows with key stakeholders (eg, Product, Engineering, Legal, and other cross-functional teams). (149461) &#xa0;The following&#xa0; Global Outsourcing Program Manager &#xa0;position: Responsible for establishing technical solutions to manage global outsourcing operations. Position requires 15% travel. (4300)
 &#xa0;
 For full information and to apply online, visit us at the Facebook Careers page www.facebookcareers.com or navigate to our careers site on the Facebook About page about.facebook.com&#xa0;and click on Careers.
 &#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 12:45:15 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15772937/assistant-professor-of-organizational-behavior</link>

								<title>Assistant Professor of Organizational Behavior | Carnegie Mellon University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15772937/assistant-professor-of-organizational-behavior</guid>
								<description>Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania,  The Heinz College at Carnegie Mellon University invites applications for tenure-track positions at the assistant professor level who are pursuing research programs on how people, teams and organizations are responding to technology and policy induced changes to work practices.&#xa0; The College is home to the University&#39;s School of Information Systems and Management and its School of Public Policy and Management - a unique co-location of IT, Public Policy and Management. The college has highly ranked undergraduate, masters and doctoral programs at the nexus of public policy and management as well as in information systems and management.
 Successful candidates will have outstanding research abilities and be committed to achieving excellence in teaching. The College houses research centers that enable deep engagement with organizations (see the PwC Center at&#xa0; https://www.cmu.edu/risk-reg-center/ )&#xa0; and policy makers (see the Block Center at&#xa0; https://www.cmu.edu/block-center/ ) concerned with the future of work. The college is well known for its collegial, interdisciplinary and supportive culture and excellence both within and across disciplines relevant to this search.
 The college has close ties via research centers, student advising, and faculty collaborations with the Tepper School of Business, Department of Machine Learning, and the Department of Social and Decision Sciences at the Dietrich College. The candidate must have obtained, or expect to obtain shortly, a PhD or equivalent degree in Management, Organization Science, Organizational Behavior, Organizational Psychology or a related social science. Applications will be accepted through December 31, 2021.</description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 12:18:24 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15766137/lecturer-assistant-professor-in-management-x2-ucd-college-of-business-5-year-fixed-term</link>

								<title>Lecturer/ Assistant Professor in Management x2, UCD College of Business, 5 year fixed-term  | UCD</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15766137/lecturer-assistant-professor-in-management-x2-ucd-college-of-business-5-year-fixed-term</guid>
								<description>Dublin, Ireland,  Applications are invited for a&#xa0; 5 year fixed-term contract &#xa0;posts of&#xa0; Lecturer/ Assistant Professor in Management x2 &#xa0;within&#xa0; UCD College of Business
 University College Dublin invites applications for the position of Lecturer/Assistant Professor in the UCD College of Business, Management Subject Area. There are two posts to be filled on a five-year basis. The areas of focus for these posts are specifically those of Technology Management and Innovation &#38; Leading Innovation.
 &#xa0;
 UCD College of Business consists of the UCD Lochlann Quinn School of Business (&#8216;the Quinn School&#8217;) focused on undergraduate education, the UCD Michael Smurfit Graduate School of Business (&#8216;the Smurfit School&#8217;), the UCD Centre for Distance Learning (&#8216;CDL&#8217;) and UCD Smurfit Executive Development (&#8216;Executive Development&#8217;). The Quinn School and CDL are located on the main campus at Belfield while the Smurfit School and Executive Development are located at Blackrock about five kilometres away. Academic staff teach typically teach across all schools.
 &#xa0;
 The successful candidate will have a proven track record and will provide leadership in the following areas:
 &#xa0;
 Research: &#xa0;The Management Subject Area places a strong emphasis on research leading to publication in international, peer-reviewed academic journals and in leading debate in the academic and public space. Candidates should have established a track record of research in innovation, technology management, technological disruptions, innovation teams, leading innovation, and/or cognate areas with publications in international, peer-reviewed academic journals in these and other related management fields.
 &#xa0;
 Teaching and Learning: &#xa0;The Management Subject Area makes a significant contribution to the College&#8217;s undergraduate and postgraduate teaching including in particular our Undergraduate programmes &#8211; the BComm, the BComm (International), and Bachelor of Business and Law, the wide range of specialist master programmes, the MBA, Executive Education and the PhD programme.
 &#xa0;
 Administration: &#xa0;assume administrative and managerial duties as appropriate to the role.
 &#xa0;
 Lecturer/Asst Professor Above The Bar Salary Scale: &#xa0;&#xa0; 55,397 - 87,724 per annum 
 Appointment will be made on scale and in accordance with the Department of Finance guidelines.
 Closing date: &#xa0;17:00hrs (local Irish time) on&#xa0; 7th January 2022
 Applications must be submitted by the closing date and time specified. Any applications which are still in progress at the closing time of 17:00hrs (Local Irish Time) on the specified closing date will be cancelled automatically by the system. UCD are unable to accept late applications.
 UCD do not require assistance from Recruitment Agencies. Any CV&#39;s submitted by Recruitment Agencies will be returned.
 &#xa0;
 Note: Hours of work for academic staff are those as prescribed under Public Service Agreements. For further information please follow link below:
 https://www.ucd.ie/hr/t4media/Academic%20Contract.pdf .
 &#xa0;
 Prior to application, further information (including application procedure) should be obtained from the Work at UCD website: https://www.ucd.ie/workatucd/jobs/.</description>
								<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 06:26:40 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15783976/lecturer-logistics-and-supply-chain-management-sgs-campus</link>

								<title>Lecturer Logistics and Supply Chain Management, SGS Campus | RMIT Vietnam</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15783976/lecturer-logistics-and-supply-chain-management-sgs-campus</guid>
								<description>Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam,  RMIT Vietnam
 RMIT Vietnam , an entity of RMIT University, has campuses in Ho Chi Minh City and Hanoi since 2001. We provide internationally recognised, high-quality, education and professional training for students, clients and the community, and assist in the development of human resources capability in Vietnam and the region by hosting students from Australia and many other countries.
 School of Business and Management
 RMIT Vietnam&#8217;s School of Business and Management has established a reputation for excellence in business and management education, providing high quality, industry responsive programs relevant to the national and global marketplace.
 We deliver work ready graduates. In today&#8217;s competitive environment, professionals need the skills to adapt to an ever-changing business world. With RMIT Vietnam&#39;s close partnerships with industry, our students are engaged with some of industry&#8217;s top business people, receiving knowledge and skills aligned directly with their specific career paths. At RMIT Vietnam, we give our students the skills to address real-world business issues.
 The role&#xa0;and responsibilities
 As a Lecturer you will contribute to the teaching and research efforts of RMIT Vietnam across disciplines related to Logistics and Supply Chain Management. Specifically, you will teach within undergraduate, Masters and Graduate Diploma programs whilst advancing and developing your research and professional capabilities. You will actively promote the program by establishing and maintaining memberships, links and partnerships with academic, industry and professional communities and work and connect collaboratively with fellow academics within the teaching team, sharing updates and advances on developments in your field and  specialisation.  You may also have the opportunities to coordinate courses.
 For a more detailed account of the position responsibilities, you can click on the following link:
 &#xa0; B&#38;I_Lecturer, Logistics &#38; Supply Chain_Oct 2019.pdf Key selection criteria
 PhD/DBA in Logistics and Supply Chain Management, or equivalent relevant Doctoral qualification. In depth knowledge of the disciplines mentioned above, specifically in the Logistics and Supply Chain Management and Information Systems. Demonstrated ability to prepare and deliver programs at undergraduate and post-graduate levels, including online delivery, and the ability to produce high quality curriculum or program materials. Emerging or established research background; publications, development of new research initiatives, competitive research funding, and industry links. Ability to generate alternative funding projects through effective liaison with industry and government. Excellent interpersonal and communications skills to effectively collaborate with fellow colleagues, research candidates and students, industry connections with a keen sense and commitment teamwork. Proven track record regarding maximising positive student outcomes, experience and feedback.
 Benefits for successful applicants:


 Highly competitive VND salary (plus allowances) for  Vietnamese candidates  or attractive USD salary package (plus benefits) for  expatriate candidates&#xa0; depending on proven track record in meeting all the key selection criteria.


 Commitment to ongoing professional and personal development.


 20 days annual leave plus two University public holidays plus 5 days paid Xmas closure (in addition to standard national public holidays) plus 10 days sick leave per annum.


 Expatriate candidates : Relocation allowance + flight (for expatriates relocating from outside Vietnam) + reimbursement of all work permit and visa related costs + private medical insurance + annual health check


 Vietnamese candidates : 13th month Tet bonus + private medical insurance + annual health check.


 Free on-site gym facilities plus variety of well-being and fitness classes available to staff.


 Access to extensive international online library and resources


 Undergraduate education fee support for dependents after a two-year qualifying period.


 Further information


 English is the language of teaching and communication at RMIT Vietnam. For this role, the minimum requirement is IELTS 7.0


 As an expatriate candidate you will require a work permit to be employed in Vietnam.&#xa0; To qualify for a work permit you will need a PhD qualification and you will need to be able to demonstrate at least 5 years of teaching related subject in a tertiary education environment.


 Academic FAQ&#39;s RMIT Vietnam 2018.pdf
 NEW Information Pack - Foreign Candidates - Academic 2018.pdf
 How to apply
 Click on the &#8216;Apply Now&#8217; link.
 Applications Close:
 29th November, 2021 11.59 pm</description>
								<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 03:38:03 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15786544/tenure-track-senior-business-faculty</link>

								<title>Tenure-Track Senior Business Faculty | Hollins University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15786544/tenure-track-senior-business-faculty</guid>
								<description>Roanoke, Virginia,  Hollins University in Roanoke, Virginia invites applications for a tenure-track, experienced business faculty member. &#xa0; This is a full-time, open rank and business sub-field&#xa0;position&#xa0;beginning July 1, 2022.&#xa0;Please visit this&#xa0; web page &#xa0;to learn more about Hollins; its commitment to diversity, equity, inclusion, and justice; faculty development;&#xa0;the university&#8217;s students;&#xa0;and the Roanoke Valley.&#xa0;
 Position &#38; Qualifications
 The Department of Economics and Business strives to prepare students for leadership positions in a global society and offers a major in economics and tracks in general business, international business, finance, and a new entrepreneurship track, along with business and international business minors, and a new minor in entrepreneurship. This position carries a teaching load of three undergraduate courses per semester. Other duties include maintaining scholarly activity in the form of publications and presentations; developing curriculum; advising, mentoring, and recruiting students; participating in department and university service; and engaging with the vibrant local Roanoke Valley business community.&#xa0;
 The successful candidate will have a strong record of innovative, student-centered teaching at the undergraduate level, evidence of scholarly accomplishment, demonstrated leadership in business curriculum development, and a strong commitment to the liberal arts and women&#8217;s education. They will be able to teach introduction to business, international business, and business law and ethics, in addition to other required and elective courses in business, such as organizational behavior, marketing, e-commerce, and entrepreneurship. The ideal candidate will hold a Ph.D. in business, business economics, marketing, or organizational behavior or a D.B.A.
 Hollins seeks to recruit and retain outstanding candidates who exhibit a clear commitment to diversity, equity, and inclusion and who will enhance the diversity of its faculty and staff. As such, the successful candidate will have the exciting opportunity to partner with department faculty to help lead the business curriculum and to infuse it with a newly invigorated vision that includes the cultivation of women&#8217;s leadership; experiential learning and career preparedness; and diversity, equity, inclusion, and justice. In alignment with institutional and programmatic priorities, the business program is also poised to take full advantage of cross-disciplinary partnerships with academic programs across campus and in the Roanoke community to develop the next generation of successful women business leaders.
 About Hollins
 Hollins University is one of the nation&#8217;s most dynamic and diverse historically women&#8217;s colleges with an undergraduate student population that includes 33% US-American students of color, 37% Pell-eligible students, 38% first-generation college students, and 9% international students. Known for its creative and highly engaged student body and its commitment to inclusive academic excellence, Hollins prides itself on its nationally recognized and award-winning undergraduate and gender-inclusive graduate academic programs, its deeply committed alumnae/i&#xa0;network, its extraordinarily beautiful campus surrounded by the Blue Ridge Mountains, and its unique ability to ensure that each of its students has the opportunity to design a transformational college experience.&#xa0;&#xa0;
 Hollins University is highly ranked for student participation in alumni network (#5 private schools, Princeton Review&#8217;s  Best Value Colleges for 2021 ), internships (#12 private schools, Princeton Review&#8217;s  Best Value Colleges for 2021 ), and social mobility (#16 in  U.S. News Best Colleges 2022 ). Hollins University&#8217;s  Batten Leadership Institute  and the  Rutherfoord Center for Experiential Learning  provide students with robust access to multiple networking and career preparedness opportunities from leadership development to internships to study abroad.
 Application Process
 Screening of candidates will begin November 15, 2021; the search will remain open until the position is filled. To apply, please submit the following materials:&#xa0;

 A cover letter that includes your vision for and experience with supporting and growing a business program uniquely dedicated to serving women;
 A curriculum vitae; and&#xa0;
 A diversity, equity, and inclusion statement that addresses how you promote inclusivity, bring in diverse perspectives, and/or discuss racial, diversity, and equality issues in your teaching, writing, research, and/or service.

 Candidates advanced to the second&#xa0;stage&#xa0;of&#xa0;review&#xa0;will be invited to submit the following materials:&#xa0;

 Three letters of recommendation (at least&#xa0;one of which must focus specifically on the candidate&#8217;s teaching experience and abilities);
 A writing sample;
 Three&#xa0;sample syllabi;&#xa0;
 Teaching evaluations;&#xa0;and
 Unofficial&#xa0;copy of graduate school transcripts.?&#xa0;

 Applicants should submit materials&#xa0;via this&#xa0; web page &#xa0;( https://hollins.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_efHrJZGKfXXG8Ga
 ).&#xa0;The selected candidate will be asked to submit official transcripts to the Office of the Provost and will also be subject to a criminal history background check. For any questions and confidential inquiries about the position, please contact Laura Hawley, Assistant to the Provost, at  lhawley@hollins.edu .&#xa0;
 Hollins is an equal opportunity employer and is strongly committed to promoting diversity and inclusivity at every level of the university. Persons of all genders; persons with disabilities; persons of all racial, ethnic, and cultural backgrounds; and first-generation college graduates are encouraged to apply.&#xa0;&#xa0;
 &#xa0; The successful candidate will have a strong record of innovative, student-centered teaching at the undergraduate level, evidence of scholarly accomplishment, demonstrated leadership in business curriculum development, and a strong commitment to the liberal arts and women&#8217;s education. They will be able to teach introduction to business, international business, and business law and ethics, in addition to other required and elective courses in business, such as organizational behavior, marketing, e-commerce, and entrepreneurship. The ideal candidate will hold a Ph.D. in business, business economics, marketing, or organizational behavior or a D.B.A.
 Hollins seeks to recruit and retain outstanding candidates who exhibit a clear commitment to diversity, equity, and inclusion and who will enhance the diversity of its faculty and staff. As such, the successful candidate will have the exciting opportunity to partner with department faculty to help lead the business curriculum and to infuse it with a newly invigorated vision that includes the cultivation of women&#8217;s leadership; experiential learning and career preparedness; and diversity, equity, inclusion, and justice. In alignment with institutional and programmatic priorities, the business program is also poised to take full advantage of cross-disciplinary partnerships with academic programs across campus and in the Roanoke community to develop the next generation of successful women business leaders.</description>
								<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 13:38:27 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15783845/lecturer-senior-lecturers-for-hrm-program-sgs-or-hanoi-campus</link>

								<title>Lecturer / Senior Lecturers for HRM Program (SGS or Hanoi Campus) | RMIT Vietnam</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15783845/lecturer-senior-lecturers-for-hrm-program-sgs-or-hanoi-campus</guid>
								<description>Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam,  RMIT VIETNAM
 RMIT Vietnam , an entity of RMIT University, has campuses in Ho Chi Minh City and Hanoi since 2001. We provide internationally recognised, high-quality, education and professional training for students, clients and the community, and assist in the development of human resources capability in Vietnam and the region by hosting students from Australia and many other countries.
 SCHOOL OF BUSINESS AND MANAGEMENT
 RMIT Vietnam&#8217;s School of Business and Management has established a reputation for excellence in business and management education, providing high quality, industry responsive programs relevant to the national and global marketplace. Department of Management includes disciplines: Management, Human Resources Management &#38; Entrepreneurship, International Business, Tourism &#38; Hospitality Management, Business Administration.
 We deliver work ready graduates. In today&#8217;s competitive environment, professionals need the skills to adapt to an ever-changing business world. With RMIT Vietnam&#39;s close partnerships with industry, our students are engaged with some of industry&#8217;s top business people, receiving knowledge and skills aligned directly with their specific career paths. At RMIT Vietnam, we give our students the skills to address real-world business issues.
 HRM AT RMIT
 RMIT University, a thought leader in Human Resource Management education, with strong industry connections and a global teaching staff, will be collaborating with Lee Hecht Harrison, world-class talent management consultancy firm to deliver this 5-day intensive course &quot;Contemporary Professional HRM practices&quot;. This course is appropriate for HR professionals who would like to complement their on-the-job experience with formal learning; or professionals in other fields interested in a career change to HR.
 YOUR ROLE
 When you join our HRM Program Team, as either a Lecturer or Senior Lecturer, you will bring your expert knowledge, education and experience to add significant value and impact to the teaching, research and industry engagement related activities involved in this role. As an academic member of staff, you can expect to team across undergraduate, Masters and Graduate Diploma programs whilst developing your own scholarly, research and professional capabilities. You will actively promote the HRM program through establishing and maintaining networks and partnerships with academic, industry and professional communities (locally and internationally).
 For a more detailed insight into the role please view the JD.
 &#xa0; SBM_Senior Lecturer, HRM_June 2019.pdf &#xa0; OUR REQUIREMENTS

 Relevant Ph.D.
 Proven teaching experience in Human Resource Management. (Foreign candidates must have at least 5 years of teaching experience at University level, to qualify for a work permit).
 Industry or professional experience in HRM related areas with ability to work with external partners, industries and organisations. &#xa0;
 Well established and consistent internationally ranked publication record for Senior Lecturer appointment.
 Highly rated performance relating to student outcomes, student experience and feedback
 Excellent team player
 Culturally adept and agile.

 BENEFITS

 Highly competitive VND salary (plus allowances) for  Vietnamese candidates  or attractive USD salary package (plus benefits) for  expatriate candidates&#xa0; depending on proven track record in meeting all the key selection criteria.
 Expatriate candidates : Relocation allowance upon commencement of role (with support to relocate overseas candidate (and family) from home location to Vietnam under current global COVID19 restrictions) + private medical insurance
 Vietnamese candidates : 13th month Tet bonus + private medical insurance + annual health check.
 20 days annual leave plus 5 days paid leave Xmas closure, plus public holidays and paid sick leave.
 Support and guidance from experienced Mobility Advisor to assist in work permit and visa application together with relocation to and settling into living and working in Vietnam.

 FURTHER INFO
 As an expatriate candidate you will require a work permit to be employed in Vietnam.&#xa0; To qualify for a work permit you will need a PhD qualification and you will need to be able to demonstrate at least 5 years of teaching HRM related subject in a tertiary education environment.
 English is the language of teaching and communication at RMIT Vietnam. For this role, the minimum requirement is IELTS Academic 7.0 and with no band less than 6.5 (or equivalent).
 Hanoi and HCMC based positions for Lecturer and Senior Lecturer roles
 &#xa0; Academic FAQ&#39;s RMIT Vietnam 2018.pdf
 &#xa0; NEW Information Pack - Foreign Candidates - Academic 2018.pdf
 Applications Close:
 29th November, 2021 11.59 pm</description>
								<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 03:32:23 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15783655/senior-lecturer-management-hcmc</link>

								<title>Senior Lecturer, Management (HCMC) | RMIT Vietnam</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15783655/senior-lecturer-management-hcmc</guid>
								<description>Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam,  RMIT Vietnam
 RMIT Vietnam , an entity of RMIT University, has campuses in Ho Chi Minh City and Hanoi since 2001. We provide internationally recognized, high-quality, education and professional training for students, clients and the community, and assist in the development of human resources capability in Vietnam and the region by hosting students from Australia and many other countries.
 SCHOOL OF BUSINESS AND MANAGEMENT
 RMIT Vietnam&#8217;s School of Business and Management has established a reputation for excellence in business and management education, providing high quality, industry responsive programs relevant to the national and global marketplace. Department of Management includes disciplines: Management, Human Resources Management &#38; Entrepreneurship, International Business, Tourism &#38; Hospitality Management, Business Administration.
 We deliver work ready graduates. In today&#8217;s competitive environment, professionals need the skills to adapt to an ever-changing business world. With our close partnerships with industry, our students are engaged with some of industry&#8217;s top business people, receiving knowledge and skills aligned directly with their specific career paths. At RMIT Vietnam, we give our students the skills to address real-world business issues.
 YOUR ROLE
 When you join our Management Program Team, as either a Lecturer or Senior Lecturer, you will bring your expert knowledge, education and experience to add significant value and impact to the teaching, research and industry engagement related activities involved in this role. As an academic member of staff, you can expect to team across undergraduate and post graduate programs whilst developing your own scholarly, research and professional capabilities. You will actively promote the program through establishing and maintaining networks and partnerships with academic, industry and professional communities (locally and internationally).
 For a more detailed insight into the role please view the JD.
 &#xa0; MGMT_Lecturer, Management.Hanoi.pdf OUR REQUIREMENTS


 Relevant Ph.D.


 Proven teaching experience in Management related courses, such a Strategic Management, Leadership, Organisation Behavior, SME and family business ownership etc. (Foreign candidates must have at least 5 years of teaching experience at University level, to qualify for a work permit).


 Industry or professional experience relevant to your discipline with ability to work with external partners, industries and organisations.


 Well established and consistent internationally ranked publication record for Senior Lecturer appointment.


 Highly rated performance relating to student outcomes, student experience and feedback


 Excellent team player


 Culturally adept and agile.


 BENEFITS


 Highly competitive VND salary (plus allowances) for  local candidates  or attractive USD salary package (plus benefits) for  expatriate candidates&#xa0; depending on proven track record in meeting all the key selection criteria.


 Expatriate candidates : Relocation allowance upon commencement of role (with support to relocate overseas candidate (and family) from home location to Vietnam under current global COVID19 restrictions) + private medical insurance


 Local candidates : 13th month Tet bonus + private medical insurance (for you and your dependents) + annual health check.


 20 days annual leave plus 5 days paid leave Xmas closure, plus public holidays and paid sick leave.


 Support and guidance from experienced Mobility Advisor to assist in work permit and visa application together with relocation to and settling into living and working in Vietnam.


 FURTHER INFO
 As an expatriate candidate you will require a work permit to be employed in Vietnam.&#xa0; To qualify for a work permit you will need a PhD qualification and you will need to be able to demonstrate at least 5 years of teaching across relevant subjects in a tertiary education environment.
 English is the language of teaching and communication at RMIT Vietnam. For this role, the minimum requirement is IELTS Academic 7.0 and with no band less than 6.5 (or equivalent).&#xa0;
 &#xa0; Academic FAQ&#39;s RMIT Vietnam 2018.pdf
 &#xa0; NEW Information Pack - Foreign Candidates - Academic 2018.pdf
 HOW TO APPLY
 Please submit your CV, covering letter, and a separate document addressing the Key Selection criteria by clicking on the &#8216; Apply &#8217; link below.&#xa0;
 Applications Close:
 29th November, 2021 11.59 pm</description>
								<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 03:17:45 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15786719/vice-president-of-advancement</link>

								<title>Vice President of Advancement | Answers in Genesis, Inc.</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15786719/vice-president-of-advancement</guid>
								<description>Petersburg, Kentucky,  The VP of Advancement holds the primary responsibility to provide vision and leadership of the ministry&#39;s comprehensive advancement goals and efforts in collaboration with the CEO and President and in alignment with the strategic plans/goals of the ministry. The position oversees the advancement team, including regional advancement officers, and is a part of the ministry&#39;s senior leadership team. This position is expected to exhibit our Core Values of SERVE when interfacing with both internal and external customers to ensure that the message and mission of Answers in Genesis is portrayed in an effective and God-honoring fashion.
 &#xa0;
 Responsibilities

 Promote the mission and standards of Answers in Genesis.
 Create a SERVE culture environment in all work done.
 Develop and manage a comprehensive multi-year advancement strategic plan with milestones to achieve progress toward short-term and long-term fundraising goals to support annual giving, major capital campaigns, and other ministry initiatives in collaboration with the CEO and President.
 Lead and motivate the Advancement team from concept to completion on fundraising goals ensuring accurate, high quality and consistent communication with donors.
 Serve as a spokesperson for the ministry at a variety of donor events.
 Develop, implement, and evaluate an annual donor communications calendar.
 Oversee all general donor activities to include the following: general monthly direct mail solicitations, electronic communications, and lapse donor campaigns.
 Oversee all aspects of the CEO&#39;s monthly letter to supporters to ensure that it is completed and delivered in a timely manner.
 Lead and develop fundraising engagement through AiG&#39;s web sites, social media, and email communications.
 Leveraging the significant attendance at the Ark Encounter and Creation Museum, evaluate, develop, and implement new and existing donor acquisition, engagement, and retention activities to grow, enhance and retain AiG&#39;s base of support.
 Oversee onsite and regional in-person fundraising events with ministry donors.
 Personally, participate in top-level fundraising activities, including identification and cultivation of major donor relationships.
 Host donors and other VIP friends of the ministry at the Ark Encounter and Creation Museum.
 Coordinate with AiG&#39;s in-house legal counsel on planned giving opportunities, the marketing thereof, and engagement of supporters with these opportunities directly through the regional advancement officers.
 Provide oversight and evaluation of ongoing donor recognition. This includes the following: thank- you phone calls, prayer cards, general thank you letters and special recognition efforts.
 Develop and distribute regular performance tracking and management reports to keep AiG leadership and other stakeholders informed and updated on advancement campaigns, activities, and progress against goals.
 Identify resources needed for capital fundraising campaigns and assign individuals to execute work
 Manage funding activities that interface with donors such as Ark/Creation Museum lifetime membership campaigns, bond issues, and other opportunities.
 And all other duties and responsibilities as assigned by management.


 Bachelor&#39;s degree.
 10+ years&#39; of progressive advancement experience, or an equivalent combination of related experience and education.
 10+ years&#39; leadership/management experience with 5+ years leading the fundraising or advancement function desired.
 A consistent record of developing and managing successful advancement activities including: major gift campaigns, web and social media fundraising activities, planned giving, direct mail as well as cultivating diverse funding streams.
 Extensive knowledge of advancement principles and understanding of ECFA fundraising standards.
 Outstanding interpersonal skills and the proven ability to work with diverse groups including staff, community and Christian leaders/pastors, and donors.
 Gifted in verbal and written communication with the ability to serve as a spokesperson for the ministry
 Knowledge and previous use of donor software
 Experience in building an endowment preferred
 Excellent computer skills &#8211; proficient in Microsoft Office suite (Excel, Word, etc).

 Items Needed for Possible Employment

 Completion of on-line application, https://answersingenesis.org
 Salary Requirements
 Salvation Testimony
 Creation Belief Statement
 Confirmation of your agreement with the AiG Statement of Faith
 Completion of a Background Check and Pre-Employment Drug Screen

 Apply Here
 PI153910393</description>
								<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 15:37:06 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15783348/business-school-of-sun-yat-sen-university</link>

								<title>Business School of Sun Yat-sen University | Sun Yat-sen University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15783348/business-school-of-sun-yat-sen-university</guid>
								<description>Shenzhen, China,  Sun Yat-sen University, founded by Dr. Sun Yat-sen and with an educational tradition spanning over 100 years, is a preeminent research, academic and cultural center and the premier location for talent development in South China. Sun Yat-sen University has developed into a modern comprehensive university that enjoys a reputation as a top-tier university nationally and a renowned university internationally. With five campuses in the three cities of Guangzhou, Zhuhai and Shenzhen, and ten affiliated hospitals, the University is becoming a world-class university and global center of learning.&#xa0;
 Business School of Sun Yat-sen University is a newly established college, located in Shenzhen, China. Business School seeks to fill faculty positions at the levels of Assistant/Associate/Professor of Economics/Finance/Accounting/Management, beginning in fall 2021.&#xa0; Candidates for full professor/associate professor should provide evidence of publications in reputable academic journals. Prior experience in research grant is preferably desirable.
 Successful candidates for assistant professor positions should possess a Ph.D. and have a high research potential.
 Application Instructions:
 All applicants must submit the following documents to search committee chair, Prof. Guangzhong Li at&#xa0; bsjob@mail.sysu.edu.cn . The recruitment information is long-term valid.
 *Cover letter
 *Current resume
 *Three reference letters
 *Sample of current research
 *Evidence of teaching effectiveness Compensation is competitive with leading Asian Business Schools. Attractive start-up research fund and setting-in allowance will be provided. Social welfare benefits include subsidies for housing (including rental, relocation housing, etc.), social insurance, housing accumulation fund, health care, high quality educational resources for children, etc.</description>
								<pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 09:30:49 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15773003/dean-of-the-argyros-school-of-business-and-economics</link>

								<title>Dean of the Argyros School of Business and Economics | Chapman University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15773003/dean-of-the-argyros-school-of-business-and-economics</guid>
								<description>Orange, California,  Chapman University  | Dean of the  Argyros School of Business and Economics
 Orange, California
 Chapman University is seeking an entrepreneurial, creative, collaborative, and strategic leader to serve as the Dean of the Argyros School of Business and Economics. The next Dean will have the extraordinary opportunity to lead Chapman&#8217;s fast-moving, AACSB-accredited School of Business and Economics. The Argyros School is ranked among the Top 100 Business Schools by  U.S. News &#38; World Report . The next Dean will find a school on an upward trajectory of growth and innovation centrally located in Orange County, CA. Reporting to Provost Bouchard, the Dean will lead 80 full-time tenure-line faculty, 40 part-time faculty, and a 25 full-time staff.
 The incoming Dean will be responsible for providing creative vision and inspiring leadership for the School while also creating transcollegiate initiatives across the university, through the Southern California region, and on the national stage. The Dean will work closely with both internal and external constituencies to provide even greater opportunities for students and faculty, to further the educational and research mission of the School, and to ensure its continued positive momentum and growth. The Dean oversees a school comprising of 1,900 undergraduate and 210 graduate students. The new Dean will have the opportunity to continue to: elevate the School&#8217;s mission and actively recruit exceptional students and employees; further build productive partnerships and connections for the School in the business community; advance diversity and inclusion within the School and across campus; and build and support continued momentum around philanthropic success of the School.
 Candidate Profile &#xa0;
 The successful candidate will&#xa0;bring a record of academic and leadership excellence that commands the respect of the academic community and meets the criteria for appointment as a tenured full professor at Chapman. In addition,&#xa0;the incoming Dean will possess many of the following abilities, attributes, and experiences:&#xa0;

 An entrepreneurial and energetic approach to leadership in an academic setting;
 A keen understanding of the changing landscape for business education nationally, as well as deep familiarity with current trends in academic program development and delivery (online, hybrid, etc.);
 A passion and eagerness to fundraise to support the School&#8217;s mission;
 A natural ability and desire to build trusting relationships with faculty and to facilitate shared governance without stifling opportunities for innovation;
 Demonstrated commitment and practical experience with creating, maintaining, and ensuring an inclusive and welcoming climate in which people of all backgrounds can thrive;
 Experience with AACSB accreditation standards and requirements at a high level;
 Exposure to and appreciation for the use of technology in creating and delivering outstanding academic programs;
 The ability to lead a complex organization to the next level of success with integrity;

 To view the full position description please visit this&#xa0; website .&#xa0;&#xa0;
 Contact &#xa0;
 Amy Sugin, Jim Sirianni, Mark Halligan, and Holly Bogo of&#xa0;Koya Partners, a part of Diversified Search, have&#xa0;been retained by Chapman University to assist in this search process. Applications, nominations, and further inquiries should be directed to&#xa0; ArgyrosDean@koyapartners.com .
 &#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;..
 Chapman University is an equal opportunity employer committed to fostering a diverse and inclusive academic global community. The university is dedicated to enhancing diversity and inclusion in all aspects of recruitment and employment. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, age, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, gender expression, national origin, ancestry, citizenship status, physical disability, mental disability, medical condition, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, genetic information or any other characteristic protected by state or federal law. The university is committed to achieving a diverse faculty and staff and encourages members of underrepresented groups to apply.</description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 13:08:21 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15767684/job-title-clinical-assistant-professor-position-in-organization-leadership-16520</link>

								<title>Job Title: Clinical Assistant Professor Position in Organization Leadership 16520 | Purdue University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15767684/job-title-clinical-assistant-professor-position-in-organization-leadership-16520</guid>
								<description>West Lafayette, Indiana,  Assistant Professor
 The Technology Leadership and Innovation Department at Purdue University is inviting applicants for a faculty position at the Clinical Assistant Professor rank. This is a 9-month non-tenure track position to begin in August 2022. Candidates must have an earned doctorate in human resource development (HRD), human resources management (HRM), Industrial-Organizational Psychology (I/O Psychology), or related fields.
 &#xa0;
 Position Responsibilities
 The successful candidate will be expected to teach in project management and related areas. They will also be expected to participate in service activities at the program, department, college, university, community, as well as within relevant professional organizations. The candidate will teach in the areas of project management, leadership, and human resource development at the undergraduate or graduate levels. We are seeking a candidate with a strong foundation and experience in industry-based project management. Qualifications

 A Ph.D. in Human Resource Development (HRD), Human Resources Management (HRM), or Industrial-Organizational Psychology (I/O Psychology), Management, Industrial Engineering, or related field, either completed or expected to be completed by August 2022.
 Project Management Professional certification.
 Strong evidence of teaching excellence
 Ability to work collegially as part of a team.

 &#xa0;
 Preferred Qualifications

 Previous employment/consulting experience in corporations, non-profit or public sector organizations.
 Experience with technologies impacting organizations and the workplace.

 &#xa0;
 Program/Unit Description
 The Department of Technology Leadership &#38; Innovation is part of the Purdue Polytechnic, one of the 10 academic colleges on Purdue University&#8217;s flagship campus in West Lafayette, IN. &#xa0;The department is a leader in advancing knowledge about human resource development, organizational leadership, technology, and innovation in local, national, and international contexts. Our research and teaching reflect a commitment to interdisciplinary collaboration, and engagement with businesses, organizations, and corporations, seeking to enhance employee expertise and organizational capacities around the globe.&#xa0; The department faculty has a strong track record in external funded grants including NSF, DOL, NIJ, DHS, USDA, USDS as well as corporations and foundations.&#xa0; The Technology Leadership &#38; Innovation department is committed to advancing diversity in all areas of faculty effort, including scholarship, instruction, and engagement. Additional information about the Purdue Polytechnic Institute and the Department can be found at https://polytechnic.purdue.edu/ and https://polytechnic.purdue.edu/departments/technology-leadership-innovation.
 &#xa0;
 Appointment Details

 The successful candidate will be appointed to a full-time, 9-month non&#xa0;tenure-track&#xa0;position, starting Fall 2022.
 Summer employment is a possibility but is neither guaranteed nor required.
 Salary will be competitive and commensurate with experience, including a faculty start-up package.

 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;
 Candidates must have the ability to work in the US without immigration sponsorship from Purdue University.
 &#xa0;
 Application Instructional
 A background check is required for employment in this position.
 &#xa0;
 Application Process
 All candidates need to apply through the Success Factors link found here:&#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0;https://career8.successfactors.com/sfcareer/jobreqcareer?jobId=16520&#38;company=purdueuniv
 &#xa0;
 Applications must be submitted as a single pdf file and include the following components in the order listed.&#xa0; All applications must include:

 A cover letter addressing how the candidate fits the qualifications outlined in the position description (please indicate the position requisition number of 16520&#xa0;at the beginning of the letter).
 A Curriculum Vitae.
 A statement of research interests and directions.
 A statement of teaching interests and philosophy.
 A sample article published in a scholarly venue.
 Teaching evaluations.
 Three letters of reference
 A diversity, equity and inclusion statement addressing scholarship, teaching, and engagement as a faculty member.

 &#xa0;
 Review of applications will begin on November 22, 2021, and will continue until the position is filled.&#xa0;&#xa0;Only complete applications will be given full consideration.
 &#xa0;
 Any questions about this position should be sent to the search committee chair:
 Dr. Nathalie Duval-Couetil (Search Committee Chair) (natduval@purdue.edu)
 Department of Technology Leadership, &#38; Innovation
 Purdue University
 &#xa0;
 EOE/AA
 Purdue University&#39;s Department of Technology Leadership &#38; Innovation&#xa0;is committed to advancing diversity in all areas of faculty effort, including scholarship, instruction, and engagement. Candidates should address at least one of these areas in a separate Diversity and Inclusion Statement, indicating their past experiences, current interests or activities, and/or future goals to promote a climate that values diversity and inclusion.
 &#xa0;
 Affirmative Action Statement
 Purdue University is an EOE/AA employer. All individuals, including minorities, women, individuals with disabilities, and veterans are encouraged to apply.&#xa0;
 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 17:01:25 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15767689/job-title-senior-lecturer-in-organizational-leadership-16311</link>

								<title>Job Title: Senior Lecturer in Organizational Leadership 16311 | Purdue University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15767689/job-title-senior-lecturer-in-organizational-leadership-16311</guid>
								<description>West Lafayette, Indiana,  Assistant Professor
 The Technology Leadership and Innovation Department at Purdue University is inviting applicants for a senior lecturer position. This is a 9-month non-tenure track position to begin in August 2022. Candidates must have an earned doctorate in human resource development (HRD), human resources management (HRM), Industrial-Organizational Psychology (I/O Psychology), or related fields.
 &#xa0;
 Position Responsibilities
 The successful candidate will be expected to teach in organizational leadership and related areas. They will also be expected to participate in service activities at the program, department, college, university, community, as well as within relevant professional organizations. The candidate will teach in the areas of organizational leadership, and human resource development at the undergraduate level. We are seeking a candidate with a strong foundation and experience in organizational leadership. Qualifications

 A Ph.D. in Human Resource Development (HRD), Human Resources Management (HRM), or Industrial-Organizational Psychology (I/O Psychology), Management, Industrial Engineering, or related field, either completed or expected to be completed by August 2022.
 Experience in business, companies, or corporations
 Strong evidence of teaching excellence
 Ability to work collegially as part of a team

 &#xa0;
 We will begin reviewing applications on November 22, 2021, and will continue until we fill the position.
 &#xa0;
 Applications must include:

 A cover letter addressing how the candidate fits the qualifications outlined in the position description.
 A Curriculum Vitae.
 A statement of teaching interests and philosophy.
 A sample article published in a scholarly venue.
 Teaching evaluations.
 Three letters of reference.
 A diversity, equity and inclusion statement addressing scholarship, teaching, and engagement as a faculty member.

 &#xa0;
 Preferred Qualifications
 &#xa0;

 Previous employment/consulting experience in business, companies, or corporations.
 Experience with technologies impacting organizations and the workplace.

 &#xa0;
 Program/Unit Description
 The Department of Technology Leadership &#38; Innovation is part of the Purdue Polytechnic, one of the 10 academic colleges on Purdue University&#8217;s flagship campus in West Lafayette, IN. &#xa0;The department is a leader in advancing knowledge about human resource development, organizational leadership, technology, and innovation in local, national, and international contexts. Our research and teaching reflect a commitment to interdisciplinary collaboration, and engagement with businesses, organizations, and corporations, seeking to enhance employee expertise and organizational capacities around the globe. The department faculty has a strong track record in external funded grants including NSF, DOL, NIJ, DHS, USDA, USDS as well as corporations and foundations. The Technology Leadership &#38; Innovation department is committed to advancing diversity in all areas of faculty effort, including scholarship, instruction, and engagement. Additional information about the Purdue Polytechnic Institute and the Department can be found at https://polytechnic.purdue.edu/ and https://polytechnic.purdue.edu/departments/technology-leadership-innovation.
 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;
 Appointment Details

 The successful candidate will be appointed to a full-time, 9-month non-tenure track position, starting Fall 2022.
 Summer employment is a possibility but is neither guaranteed nor required.
 Salary will be competitive and commensurate with experience.

 &#xa0;
 Candidates must have the ability to work in the US without immigration sponsorship from Purdue University.
 &#xa0;
 Application Instructions
 A background check is required for employment in this position.
 &#xa0;
 Application Process
 All candidates need to apply through the Success Factors link found here:  https://career8.successfactors.com/sfcareer/jobreqcareer?jobId=16311&#38;company=purdueuniv
 &#xa0;
 Applications must be submitted as a single pdf file and include the following components in the order listed.&#xa0; All applications must include:

 A cover letter addressing how the candidate fits the qualifications outlined in the position description (please indicate the position requisition number of 16311 at the beginning of the letter).
 A Curriculum Vitae.
 A statement of research interests and directions.
 A statement of teaching interests and philosophy.
 A sample article published in a scholarly venue.
 Teaching evaluations.
 Three letters of reference.
 A diversity, equity and inclusion statement addressing scholarship, teaching, and engagement as a faculty member.

 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;
 Review of applications will begin on November 22, 2021, and will continue until the position is filled.&#xa0;&#xa0;Only complete applications will be given full consideration.
 &#xa0;
 Any questions about this position should be sent to the search committee chair:
 Dr. Nathalie Duval-Couetil (Search Committee Chair) (natduval@purdue.edu)
 Department of Technology Leadership, &#38; Innovation
 Purdue University
 &#xa0;
 EOE/AA
 Purdue University&#39;s Department of Technology Leadership &#38; Innovation&#xa0;is committed to advancing diversity in all areas of faculty effort, including scholarship, instruction, and engagement. Candidates should address at least one of these areas in a separate Diversity and Inclusion Statement, indicating their past experiences, current interests or activities, and/or future goals to promote a climate that values diversity and inclusion.
 &#xa0;
 Affirmative Action Statement
 Purdue University is an EOE/AA employer. All individuals, including minorities, women, individuals with disabilities, and veterans are encouraged to apply.&#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 17:04:35 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15773189/assistant-professor-organizational-behavior</link>

								<title>Assistant Professor- Organizational Behavior | W. P. Carey - Department of Management &#38; Entrepreneurship</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15773189/assistant-professor-organizational-behavior</guid>
								<description>Tempe, Arizona,  The Assistant Professor opening is a tenure-track position&#xa0;in the area&#xa0;of organizational behavior. Eligible applicants must conduct high quality research that is published in the Department&#8217;s &#8220;A level&#8221; journals; effectively teach management courses at the undergraduate and/or graduate level; serve as a research mentor to doctoral students; and interact effectively with colleagues to support and enhance our unique department culture. The&#xa0;appointment&#xa0;will begin in&#xa0;Fall 2022.
 The W. P. Carey School of Business values our cultural and intellectual diversity and continually strives to foster a welcoming and inclusive environment.&#xa0; We are especially interested in applicants who can strengthen the diversity of the academic community.
 &#xa0;





 Qualifications


 Minimum Qualifications:
 1) An earned PhD&#xa0;in organizational behavior or related academic field, or must be close to earning a&#xa0;PhD&#xa0;by the position start date.&#xa0;
 2) Evidence of the potential to actively publish in premier scholarly management journals.
 Desired Qualifications:
 1) Evidence of teaching excellence in one or more areas of management.
 2) Evidence of a strong research agenda with published or forthcoming papers in premier academic journals .





 Application Instructions


 Applicants must submit curriculum vitae, cover letter that addresses the above criteria, evidence of effective university teaching, and a statement (one page maximum) addressing how your past and/or potential contributions to diversity and inclusion will advance W. P. Carey&#8217;s commitment to inclusive excellence.&#xa0;Only electronic applications will be accepted via&#xa0; http://apply.interfolio.com/98439
 Application deadline is January 3, 2022. Applications will continue to be accepted on a rolling basis for a reserve pool. Applications in the reserve pool may then be reviewed in the order in which they were received until the position is filled.
 References will be requested during the latter stages of the selection process. If you have any further questions about the position, please contact Professor Shen at 480.965.1422 or&#xa0; Wei.Shen@asu.edu .
 The &#xa0;Department of Management and Entrepreneurship &#xa0;is one of ASU&#8217;s pillars of excellence. Over the last five years, our research productivity continues to rank among the top five schools in North America in terms of publications in premier management journals (see Texas A &#38; M / UGA rankings website at http://www.tamugarankings.com). Our faculty has a strong emphasis on research excellence. We have multiple faculty members who either currently serve or have served as editor or associate editor of the top management journals, underscoring our commitment to a research-oriented culture. In addition, our faculty members are among the most award-winning teachers in the W. P. Carey School and author multiple market-leading textbooks. We are an especially collegial group, and organizational citizenship is a cornerstone of our culture.
 The faculty members in Management and Entrepreneurship represent the areas of Strategic Management, Organizational Behavior, Organizational Theory, Human Resources, International Management, Ethics/Social Environment of Business, and Entrepreneurship. They include: Blake Ashforth, Mike Baer, Jonathan Bundy, Rachel Burgess, Trevis Certo (Senior Associate Dean for Faculty), Heewon Chae, Kevin Corley, Luis Gomez-Mejia, Amy Hillman, Peter Hom, Don Lange, Peggy Lee, Jeff LePine, Marcie LePine, Luiz Mesquita (Associate Dean for Graduate Programs), Chris Neck, Matt Semadeni, Wei Shen (Department Chair), Christine Shropshire, David Waldman, Shaoqing (Milo) Wang, Ned Wellman, David Welsh, and David Zhu. Additional information about the Department of Management can be found at&#xa0; http://wpcarey.asu.edu/mgt/ .
 The&#xa0; W. P. Carey School of Business &#xa0;at Arizona State University is one of the largest business schools in the United States with more than 15,000 students and 100,000 alumni worldwide. From our world-renowned faculty representing six continents to thousands of outstanding students who join us every year, the W. P. Carey School welcomes diversity and encourages global thinking. The W. P. Carey School is internationally recognized for its leadership in business education, groundbreaking research and innovation, and renowned faculty, making us one of the top-ranked business schools in the country. Learn more at wpcarey.asu.edu.
 Arizona State University &#xa0;is a new model for American higher education, an unprecedented combination of academic excellence, entrepreneurial energy and broad access. This New American University is a single, unified institution comprising four differentiated campuses positively impacting the economic, social, cultural and environmental health of the communities it serves. Its research is inspired by real world application blurring the boundaries that traditionally separate academic disciplines. ASU serves more than 70,000 students in metropolitan Phoenix, Arizona, the nation&#8217;s fifth largest city. ASU champions intellectual and cultural diversity, and welcomes students from all fifty states and more than one hundred nations across the globe.
 ASU is a tobacco-free university. For details visit www.asu.edu/tobaccofree.
 ASU conducts pre-employment screening which may include:
 Verification of work history, academic credentials, licenses, and certifications.





 Equal Employment Opportunity Statement


 A background check is required for employment. Arizona State University is a VEVRAA Federal Contractor and an Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action Employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability, protected veteran status, or any other basis protected by law. (See&#xa0; https://www.asu.edu/aad/manuals/acd/acd401.html &#xa0;and&#xa0; https://www.asu.edu/titleIX/ .)
 In compliance with federal law, ASU prepares an annual report on campus security and fire safety programs and resources.&#xa0; ASU&#8217;s Annual Security and Fire Safety Report is available online at&#xa0; https://www.asu.edu/police/PDFs/ASU-Clery-Report.pdf &#xa0; You may request a hard copy of the report by contacting the ASU Police Department at 480-965-3456.
 COVID-19 Vaccination Requirements&#xa0; - Under the recent executive order issued by President Biden requiring all employees of federal contractors to receive COVID-19 vaccinations, ASU expects all employees, including new hires, to be vaccinated unless they have an approved medical or religious accommodation.&#xa0; Proof of vaccination will be required by January 4, 2022.&#xa0; For questions about medical or religious accommodations, please&#xa0; visit the Office of Diversity, Equity and Inclusion&#8217;s webpage .</description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 15:04:12 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15767642/job-title-assistant-professor-tenure-track-in-human-resource-development-16410</link>

								<title>Job Title: Assistant Professor Tenure Track in Human Resource Development 16410 | Purdue University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15767642/job-title-assistant-professor-tenure-track-in-human-resource-development-16410</guid>
								<description>West Lafayette, Indiana,  Assistant Professor
 The Technology Leadership and Innovation Department at Purdue University is inviting applicants for a faculty position at the Assistant Professor rank. This is a 9-month tenure track position to begin in August 2022. Candidates must have an earned doctorate in human resource development (HRD), human resources management (HRM), Industrial-Organizational Psychology (I/O Psychology), or related fields.
 &#xa0;
 Position Responsibilities
 The successful candidate will be expected to teach and conduct research in the areas of job analysis and job design, and the individual and organizational performance. They will also be expected to participate in service activities at the program, department, college, university, community, as well as within relevant professional organizations. The candidate will teach in the areas of leadership and human resource development across undergraduate and graduate levels. We are seeking a candidate with a strong foundation in quantitative methods, who can contribute to high impact areas of research related to leadership and human resource development.
 The successful candidate will be expected to secure external grant funding to support an independent research program, while disseminating knowledge through high quality publications, teaching and mentorship to graduate students. Qualifications

 A Ph.D. in Human Resource Development (HRD), Human Resources Management (HRM), or Industrial-Organizational Psychology (I/O Psychology) or related field, either completed or expected to be completed by August 2022.
 Strong evidence of research productivity and teaching excellence in HRD, HRM, or I/O Psychology, including evidence of published conference proceedings, high-quality peer-reviewed journal articles, and excellent teaching ratings.
 Evidence of research experience using quantitative methods
 Evidence of potential to obtain externally funded research grants.
 Ability to work collegially as part of a team.

 &#xa0;
 Preferred Qualifications

 Previous employment/consulting experience in corporations, non-profit or public sector organizations.
 Experience with technologies impacting organizations and the workplace.

 &#xa0;
 Program/Unit Description
 The Department of Technology Leadership &#38; Innovation is part of the Purdue Polytechnic, one of the 10 academic colleges on Purdue University&#8217;s flagship campus in West Lafayette, IN. &#xa0;The department is a leader in advancing knowledge about human resource development, organizational leadership, technology, and innovation in local, national, and international contexts. Our research and teaching reflect a commitment to interdisciplinary collaboration, and engagement with businesses, organizations, and corporations, seeking to enhance employee expertise and organizational capacities around the globe. The department faculty has a strong track record in external funded grants including NSF, DOL, NIJ, DHS, USDA, USDS as well as corporations and foundations. &#xa0;The Technology Leadership &#38; Innovation department is committed to advancing diversity in all areas of faculty effort, including scholarship, instruction, and engagement. Additional information about the Purdue Polytechnic Institute and the Department can be found at https://polytechnic.purdue.edu/ and https://polytechnic.purdue.edu/departments/technology-leadership-innovation.
 Appointment Details

 The successful candidate will be appointed to a full-time, 9-month tenure-track position, starting Fall 2022.
 Summer employment is a possibility but is neither guaranteed nor required.
 Salary will be competitive and commensurate with experience, including a faculty start-up package.

 &#xa0;
 Application Details

 The successful candidate will be appointed to a full-time, 9-month tenure-track position, starting Fall 2022.
 Summer employment is a possibility but is neither guaranteed nor required.
 Salary will be competitive and commensurate with experience, including a faculty start-up package.

 &#xa0;
 Application Instructions
 A background check is required for employment in this position.
 &#xa0;
 Application Process
 All candidates need to apply through the Success Factors link found here: https://career8.successfactors.com/sfcareer/jobreqcareer?jobId=16410&#38;company=purdueuniv
 &#xa0;
 Applications must be submitted as a single pdf file and include the following components in the order listed.&#xa0; All applications must include:

 A cover letter addressing how the candidate fits the qualifications outlined in the position description (please indicate the position requisition number of 16410 at the beginning of the letter).
 A Curriculum Vitae.
 A statement of research interests and directions.
 A statement of teaching interests and philosophy.
 A sample article published in a scholarly venue.
 Teaching evaluations.
 Three letters of reference.
 A diversity, equity and inclusion statement addressing scholarship, teaching, and engagement as a faculty member.

 &#xa0;
 Review of applications will begin on November 22, 2021, and will continue until the position is filled.&#xa0;&#xa0;Only complete applications will be given full consideration.
 &#xa0;
 Any questions about this position should be sent to the search committee chair:
 Dr. Nathalie Duval-Couetil (Search Committee Chair) (natduval@purdue.edu)
 Department of Technology Leadership, &#38; Innovation
 Purdue University
 &#xa0;
 EOE/AA
 Purdue University&#39;s Department of Technology Leadership &#38; Innovation&#xa0;is committed to advancing diversity in all areas of faculty effort, including scholarship, instruction, and engagement. Candidates should address at least one of these areas in a separate Diversity and Inclusion Statement, indicating their past experiences, current interests or activities, and/or future goals to promote a climate that values diversity and inclusion.
 Affirmative Action Statement
 Purdue University is an EOE/AA employer. All individuals, including minorities, women, individuals with disabilities, and veterans are encouraged to apply.&#xa0;
 &#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 16:42:04 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15767663/job-title-assistant-professor-tenure-track-position-in-organizational-leadership-16411</link>

								<title>Job Title: Assistant Professor Tenure Track Position in Organizational Leadership 16411 | Purdue University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15767663/job-title-assistant-professor-tenure-track-position-in-organizational-leadership-16411</guid>
								<description>West Lafayette, Indiana,  Assistant Professor
 The Technology Leadership and Innovation Department at Purdue University is inviting applicants for a faculty position at the Assistant Professor rank. This is a 9-month tenure track position to begin in August 2022. Candidates must have an earned doctorate in human resource development (HRD), human resources management (HRM), Industrial-Organizational Psychology (I/O Psychology), or related fields.
 &#xa0;
 Position Responsibilities
 The successful candidate will be expected to teach and conduct research in one of the areas including business ethics, conflict resolution, or organizational communication. They will also be expected to participate in service activities at the program, department, college, university, community, as well as within relevant professional organizations. The candidate will teach in the areas of leadership and human resource development across undergraduate and graduate levels. We are seeking a candidate with a strong foundation in either qualitative or quantitative methods, who can contribute to high impact areas of research related to leadership and human resource development.
 The successful candidate will be expected to secure external grant funding to support an independent research program, while disseminating knowledge through high quality publications, teaching and mentorship to graduate students. Qualifications

 A Ph.D. in Human Resource Development (HRD), Human Resources Management (HRM), or Industrial-Organizational Psychology (I/O Psychology) or related field, either completed or expected to be completed by August 2022.
 Strong evidence of research productivity and teaching excellence in HRD, HRM, or I/O Psychology, including evidence of published conference proceedings, high-quality peer-reviewed journal articles, and excellent teaching ratings.
 Evidence of research experience using qualitative or quantitative methods
 Evidence of potential to obtain externally funded research grants.
 Ability to work collegially as part of a team.

 &#xa0;
 Preferred Qualifications

 Previous employment/consulting experience in corporations, non-profit or public sector organizations.
 Experience with technologies impacting organizations and the workplace.

 &#xa0;
 Program/Unit Description
 The Department of Technology Leadership &#38; Innovation is part of the Purdue Polytechnic, one of the 10 academic colleges on Purdue University&#8217;s flagship campus in West Lafayette, IN. &#xa0;The department is a leader in advancing knowledge about human resource development, organizational leadership, technology, and innovation in local, national, and international contexts. Our research and teaching reflect a commitment to interdisciplinary collaboration, and engagement with businesses, organizations, and corporations, seeking to enhance employee expertise and organizational capacities around the globe. The department faculty has a strong track record in external funded grants including NSF, DOL, NIJ, DHS, USDA as well as corporations and foundations. The Technology Leadership &#38; Innovation department is committed to advancing diversity in all areas of faculty effort, including scholarship, instruction, and engagement. Additional information about the Purdue Polytechnic Institute and the Department can be found at https://polytechnic.purdue.edu/ and https://polytechnic.purdue.edu/departments/technology-leadership-innovation.
 &#xa0;
 Appointment Details

 The successful candidate will be appointed to a full-time, 9-month tenure-track position, starting Fall 2022.
 Summer employment is a possibility but is neither guaranteed nor required.
 Salary will be competitive and commensurate with experience, including a faculty start-up package.
 &#xa0;

 Applications Instruction
 A background check is required for employment in this position.
 &#xa0;
 Application Process
 All candidates need to apply through the Success Factors link found here: &#xa0; https://career8.successfactors.com/sfcareer/jobreqcareer?jobId=16411&#38;company=purdueuniv
 &#xa0;
 Applications must be submitted as a single pdf file and include the following components in the order listed.&#xa0; All applications must include:

 A cover letter addressing how the candidate fits the qualifications outlined in the position description (please indicate the position requisition number of 16411 at the beginning of the letter).
 A Curriculum Vitae.
 A statement of research interests and directions.
 A statement of teaching interests and philosophy.
 A sample article published in a scholarly venue.
 Teaching evaluations.
 Three letters of reference
 A diversity, equity and inclusion statement addressing scholarship, teaching, and engagement as a faculty member.

 &#xa0;
 Review of applications will begin on November 22, 2021, and will continue until the position is filled.&#xa0;&#xa0;Only complete applications will be given full consideration.
 &#xa0;
 Any questions about this position should be sent to the search committee chair:
 Dr. Nathalie Duval-Couetil (Search Committee Chair) (natduval@purdue.edu)
 Department of Technology Leadership, &#38; Innovation
 Purdue University
 &#xa0;
 EOE/AA
 Purdue University&#39;s Department of Technology Leadership &#38; Innovation&#xa0;is committed to advancing diversity in all areas of faculty effort, including scholarship, instruction, and engagement. Candidates should address at least one of these areas in a separate Diversity and Inclusion Statement, indicating their past experiences, current interests or activities, and/or future goals to promote a climate that values diversity and inclusion.
 Affirmative Action Statement
 Purdue University is an EOE/AA employer. All individuals, including minorities, women, individuals with disabilities, and veterans are encouraged to apply.&#xa0;
 &#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 16:53:45 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15772618/assistant-professor-tenure-track-of-international-trade-or-development-economics</link>

								<title>Assistant Professor (Tenure Track) of International Trade or Development Economics  | Universit&#xe4;t St. Gallen</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15772618/assistant-professor-tenure-track-of-international-trade-or-development-economics</guid>
								<description>St. Gallen, Switzerland,  &#xab;A place where knowledge is created&#xbb;
 As a leading business university we set global standards for research and teaching by promoting integrative thought, responsible action and an entrepreneurial spirit of innovation in business and society .
 &#xa0;
 Assistant Professor (Tenure Track) of International Trade or Development Economics
 &#xa0;
 The University of St.Gallen and its School of Economics and Political Science are inviting applications for an Assistant Professorship (Tenure Track) in the fields of International Trade or Development Economics. Candidates with a policy or empirical focus are particularly encouraged to apply. Candidates should have (or aspire to establish) a track record of internationally recognized research in leading general interest or field journals. Candidates further should have proven teaching excellence.
 &#xa0;
 We seek to fill the position per August 1 st &#xa0;2022 or by mutual agreement.
 For further information, please contact Professor Dr. Reto Foellmi, Chair of the Appointments Committee ( facultyposition@unisg.ch ).
 &#xa0;
 The application should include a cover letter, curriculum vitae, teaching and research statement, list of publications, and two reference letters. Candidates should submit their application to the President of the University of St.Gallen, Professor Dr. Bernhard Ehrenzeller online via&#xa0; www.unisg.ch/professorships &#xa0;at the latest by November 30, 2021.
 &#xa0;
 The University of St.Gallen is strongly committed to promoting equal opportunities and diversity. We specifically encourage women and applicants with backgrounds underrepresented among our current senior faculty to apply.</description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 07:15:50 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15767653/job-title-assistant-professor-tenure-track-position-in-organizational-change-and-development-16414</link>

								<title>Job Title: Assistant Professor Tenure Track Position in Organizational Change and Development 16414 | Purdue University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15767653/job-title-assistant-professor-tenure-track-position-in-organizational-change-and-development-16414</guid>
								<description>West Lafayette, Indiana,  Assistant Professor
 The Technology Leadership and Innovation Department at Purdue University is inviting applicants for a faculty position at the Assistant Professor rank. This is a 9-month tenure track position to begin in August 2022. Candidates must have an earned doctorate in human resource development (HRD), human resources management (HRM), Industrial-Organizational Psychology (I/O Psychology), or related fields.
 &#xa0;
 Position Responsibilities
 The successful candidate will be expected to teach and conduct research in the areas of organizational change and development. They will also be expected to participate in service activities at the program, department, college, university, community, as well as within relevant professional organizations. The candidate will teach in the areas of leadership and human resource development across undergraduate and graduate levels. We are seeking a candidate with a strong foundation in quantitative methods, who can contribute to high impact areas of research related to leadership and human resource development.
 The successful candidate will be expected to secure external grant funding to support an independent research program, while disseminating knowledge through high quality publications, teaching and mentorship to graduate students. Qualifications

 A Ph.D. in Human Resource Development (HRD), Human Resources Management (HRM), or Industrial-Organizational Psychology (I/O Psychology) or related field, either completed or expected to be completed by August 2021.
 Strong evidence of research productivity and teaching excellence in HRD, HRM, or I/O Psychology, including evidence of published conference proceedings, high-quality peer-reviewed journal articles, and excellent teaching ratings.
 Evidence of research experience using quantitative methods
 Evidence of potential to obtain externally funded research grants.
 Ability to work collegially as part of a team.

 &#xa0;
 Preferred Qualifications

 Previous employment/consulting experience in corporations, non-profit or public sector organizations.
 Experience with technologies impacting organizations and the workplace.

 &#xa0;
 Program/Unit Description
 The Department of Technology Leadership &#38; Innovation is part of the Purdue Polytechnic, one of the 10 academic colleges on Purdue University&#8217;s flagship campus in West Lafayette, IN. &#xa0;The department is a leader in advancing knowledge about human resource development, organizational leadership, technology, and innovation in local, national, and international contexts. Our research and teaching reflect a commitment to interdisciplinary collaboration, and engagement with businesses, organizations, and corporations, seeking to enhance employee expertise and organizational capacities around the globe. The department faculty has a strong track record in external funded grants including NSF, DOL, NIJ, DHS, USDA, USDS as well as corporations and foundations.&#xa0; The Technology Leadership &#38; Innovation department is committed to advancing diversity in all areas of faculty effort, including scholarship, instruction, and engagement. Additional information about the Purdue Polytechnic Institute and the Department can be found at https://polytechnic.purdue.edu/ and  https://polytechnic.purdue.edu/departments/technology-leadership-innovation .
 &#xa0;
 Appointment Details

 The successful candidate will be appointed to a full-time, 9-month tenure-track position, starting Fall 2022.
 Summer employment is a possibility but is neither guaranteed nor required.
 Salary will be competitive and commensurate with experience, including a faculty start-up package.
 &#xa0;

 Application Instructions
 A background check is required for employment in this position.
 &#xa0;
 Application Process
 All candidates need to apply through the Success Factors link found here:  https://performancemanager8.successfactors.com/sf/jobreq?jobId=16414&#38;company=purdueuniv
 &#xa0;
 Applications must be submitted as a single pdf file and include the following components in the order listed.&#xa0; All applications must include:

 A cover letter addressing how the candidate fits the qualifications outlined in the position description (please indicate the position requisition number of 16411 at the beginning of the letter).
 A Curriculum Vitae.
 A statement of research interests and directions.
 A statement of teaching interests and philosophy.
 A sample article published in a scholarly venue.
 Teaching evaluations.
 Three letters of reference
 A diversity, equity and inclusion statement addressing scholarship, teaching, and engagement as a faculty member.

 &#xa0;
 Review of applications will begin on November 22, 2021, and will continue until the position is filled.&#xa0;&#xa0;Only complete applications will be given full consideration.
 &#xa0;
 Any questions about this position should be sent to the search committee chair:
 Dr. Nathalie Duval-Couetil (Search Committee Chair) (natduval@purdue.edu)
 Department of Technology Leadership, &#38; Innovation
 Purdue University
 &#xa0;
 EOE/AA
 Purdue University&#39;s Department of Technology Leadership &#38; Innovation is committed to advancing diversity in all areas of faculty e?ort, including scholarship, instruc on, and engagement. Candidates should address at least one of these areas in a separate Diversity and Inclusion Statement, indicating their past experiences, current interests or ac vi es, and/or future goals to promote a climate that values diversity and inclusion.
 Affirmative Action Statement
 Purdue University is an EOE/AA employer. All individuals, including minorities, women, individuals with disabilities, and veterans are encouraged to apply.&#xa0;
 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 16:48:46 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15772617/assistant-professor-tenure-track-of-microeconomics</link>

								<title>Assistant Professor (Tenure Track) of Microeconomics  | Universit&#xe4;t St. Gallen</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15772617/assistant-professor-tenure-track-of-microeconomics</guid>
								<description>St.Gallen , Switzerland,  &#xab;A place where knowledge is created&#xbb;
 As a leading business university we set global standards for research and teaching by promoting integrative thought, responsible action and an entrepreneurial spirit of innovation in business and society.
 &#xa0;
 Assistant Professor (Tenure Track) of Microeconomics
 &#xa0;
 The University of St.Gallen and its School of Economics and Political Science are inviting applications for an Assistant Professorship (Tenure Track) in the field of Microeconomics. Candidates with research interests in decision theory, applied microeconomic theory or the economics of digitization are particularly encouraged to apply. Candidates should have (or aspire to establish) a track record of internationally recognized research in leading general interest or field journals. Candidates further should have excellent teaching skills in microeconomics and the willingness to teach at all levels.
 &#xa0;
 We seek to fill this position per August 1 st &#xa0;2022 or by mutual agreement.
 For further information, please contact Professor Dr. Reto Foellmi, Chair of the Appointments Committee ( facultyposition@unisg.ch ).
 &#xa0;
 The application should include a cover letter, curriculum vitae, teaching and research statement, list of publications and two reference letters. Candidates should submit their application to the President of the University of St.Gallen, Professor Dr. Bernhard Ehrenzeller online via&#xa0; www.unisg.ch/professorships &#xa0;at the latest by November 30 th &#xa0;2021.
 &#xa0;
 The University of St.Gallen is strongly committed to promoting equal opportunities and diversity. We specifically encourage women and applicants with backgrounds underrepresented among our current senior faculty to apply.</description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 07:07:31 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15767667/job-title-assistant-professor-tenure-track-position-in-organizational-leadership-16408</link>

								<title>Job Title: Assistant Professor Tenure Track Position in Organizational Leadership 16408 | Purdue University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15767667/job-title-assistant-professor-tenure-track-position-in-organizational-leadership-16408</guid>
								<description>West Lafayette, Indiana,  Assistant Professor
 The Technology Leadership and Innovation Department at Purdue University is inviting applicants for a faculty position at the Assistant Professor rank. This is a 9-month tenure track position to begin in August 2022. Candidates must have an earned doctorate in human resource development (HRD), human resources management (HRM), Industrial-Organizational Psychology (I/O Psychology), or related fields.
 &#xa0;
 Position Responsibilities
 The successful candidate will be expected to teach and conduct research in organizational leadership. They will also be expected to participate in service activities at the program, department, college, university, community, as well as within relevant professional organizations. The candidate will teach in the areas of leadership and human resource development across undergraduate and graduate levels. We are seeking a candidate with a strong foundation in quantitative methods, who can contribute to high impact areas of research related to leadership and human resource development.
 The successful candidate will be expected to secure external grant funding to support an independent research program, while disseminating knowledge through high quality publications, teaching and mentorship to graduate students. Qualifications

 A Ph.D. in Human Resource Development (HRD), Human Resources Management (HRM), or Industrial-Organizational Psychology (I/O Psychology) or related field, either completed or expected to be completed by August 2022.
 Strong evidence of research productivity and teaching excellence in HRD, HRM, or I/O Psychology, including evidence of published conference proceedings, high-quality peer-reviewed journal articles, and excellent teaching ratings.
 Evidence of research experience using quantitative methods.
 Evidence of potential to obtain externally funded research grants.
 Ability to work collegially as part of a team.

 &#xa0;
 Preferred Qualifications

 Previous employment/consulting experience in corporations, non-profit or public sector organizations.
 Experience with technologies impacting organizations and the workplace.

 &#xa0;
 Program/Unit Description
 The Department of Technology Leadership &#38; Innovation is part of the Purdue Polytechnic, one of the 10 academic colleges on Purdue University&#8217;s flagship campus in West Lafayette, IN. &#xa0;&#xa0;The department is a leader in advancing knowledge about human resource development, organizational leadership, technology, and innovation in local, national, and international contexts. Our research and teaching reflect a commitment to interdisciplinary collaboration, and engagement with businesses, organizations, and corporations, seeking to enhance employee expertise and organizational capacities around the globe. The department faculty has a strong track record in external funded grants including NSF, DOL, NIJ, DHS, USDA, USDS as well as corporations and foundations. The Technology Leadership &#38; Innovation department is committed to advancing diversity in all areas of faculty effort, including scholarship, instruction, and engagement. Additional information about the Purdue Polytechnic Institute and the Department can be found at https://polytechnic.purdue.edu/ and  https://polytechnic.purdue.edu/departments/technology-leadership-innovation .
 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;
 Appointment Details

 The successful candidate will be appointed to a full-time, 9-month tenure-track position, starting Fall 2022.
 Summer employment is a possibility but is neither guaranteed nor required.
 Salary will be competitive and commensurate with experience, including a faculty start-up package.

 &#xa0;
 Application Instructions
 A background check is required for employment in this position.
 &#xa0;
 Application Process
 All candidates need to apply through the Success Factors link found here: &#xa0;https://career8.successfactors.com/sfcareer/jobreqcareer?jobId=16408&#38;company=purdueuniv
 &#xa0;
 Applications must be submitted as a single pdf file and include the following components in the order listed.&#xa0; All applications must include:

 A cover letter addressing how the candidate fits the qualifications outlined in the position description (please indicate the position requisition number of 16408 at the beginning of the letter).
 A Curriculum Vitae.
 A statement of research interests and directions.
 A statement of teaching interests and philosophy.
 A sample article published in a scholarly venue.
 Teaching evaluations.
 Three letters of reference.
 A diversity, equity and inclusion statement addressing scholarship, teaching, and engagement as a faculty member.

 Review of applications will begin on November 22, 2021, and will continue until the position is filled.&#xa0;&#xa0;Only complete applications will be given full consideration.
 &#xa0;
 Any questions about this position should be sent to the search committee chair:
 Dr. Nathalie Duval-Couetil (Search Committee Chair) (natduval@purdue.edu)
 Department of Technology Leadership, &#38; Innovation
 Purdue University
 &#xa0;
 EOE/AA
 Purdue University&#39;s Department of Technology Leadership &#38; Innovation&#xa0;is committed to advancing diversity in all areas of faculty effort, including scholarship, instruction, and engagement. Candidates should address at least one of these areas in a separate Diversity and Inclusion Statement, indicating their past experiences, current interests or activities, and/or future goals to promote a climate that values diversity and inclusion.
 &#xa0;
 Affirmative Action Statement
 Purdue University is an EOE/AA employer. All individuals, including minorities, women, individuals with disabilities, and veterans are encouraged to apply.&#xa0;
 &#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 16:56:15 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15773422/dean-mcdonough-center-for-leadership-and-business</link>

								<title>Dean, McDonough Center for Leadership and Business | Marietta College</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15773422/dean-mcdonough-center-for-leadership-and-business</guid>
								<description>Marietta, Ohio,  Dean, McDonough Center for Leadership and Business
 Marietta College in Marietta, Ohio invites applications, nominations, and expressions of interest for the position of Dean of the McDonough Center for Leadership and Business. The Dean will lead the unification of two of the College&#39;s central academic programs, the McDonough Center for Leadership and Business and the Brachman Department of Business and Economics.  Marietta College, chartered in 1835, is a private, coeducational, nonsectarian, undergraduate, residential, liberal arts institution with a full-time enrollment of 1,284 students. Marietta College reaffirms the liberal arts as foundational in an education of the highest quality, offering more than 50 academic majors that are designed to prepare them for a successful future. The College is located in Marietta, Ohio, population 14,027, a city of beautiful parks, two rivers, 19th-century architecture, brick streets, historical landmarks, and museums. Marietta was listed among Smithsonian Magazine&#39;s top 10 best small towns in the nation to visit.  Marietta seeks an entrepreneurial and collaborative academic leader who will build upon the strengths of both programs and leverage their complementarities to establish an innovative, dynamic, and growing new organization. The current McDonough Center is a highly regarded Leadership program that draws students from across the campus and all majors, while the Department of Business and Economics delivers academic excellence in eleven major programs. The Dean of the new McDonough Center for Leadership and Business will bring a strong academic background in leadership or a business or economics discipline, will have excellent interpersonal skills, the capacity to build consensus, and seek innovative opportunities for collaboration and program growth created by this merger.  The successful candidate will have a doctorate in Leadership, or in a Business, Economics or related discipline, and significant academic administrative experience, including curricular development. The new Dean will also bring a record of teaching and scholarship worthy of appointment at the full professor level. We seek an individual with a collaborative and transparent leadership style, excellent team-building skills, an understanding of and appreciation for Leadership as an academic discipline, and a familiarity with Business and Economics curricula. Additional information about the position and qualifications are detailed in the search profile, available for download  here .  The College is being assisted in the search by Academic Search. Applications, nominations, and expressions of interest can be submitted in confidence to  MariettaMcDonoughDean@academicsearch.org . Applications should consist of a substantive letter of interest, a curriculum vitae, and a list of five professional references with full contact information and a note indicating the nature of your working relationship with each. References will not be contacted without the explicit permission of the candidate. The position is open until filled but only applications received by January 4, 2022, can be assured full consideration. Confidential discussions about this opportunity may be arranged by contacting Stuart Dorsey  (Stuart.Dorsey@academicsearch.org) .  Marietta College is an equal opportunity educator and employer that values diversity. The College seeks to enhance the diversity of its faculty and staff. People of color, women, veterans, and persons with disabilities are strongly encouraged to apply. Marietta College does not discriminate on the basis of age, race, color, national or ethnic origin, disability, sex, gender identity, gender expression, sexual orientation, or religious affiliation. Copyright &#xa9;2021 Jobelephant.com Inc. All rights reserved. Posted by the FREE value-added recruitment advertising agency     jeid-ee69c3abb6c18f48bde65d67eb27e9a7</description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 17:18:37 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15773479/faculty-position-open-rank-in-real-estate-economics</link>

								<title>Faculty Position (Open Rank) in Real Estate Economics  | USC Sol Price School of Public Policy</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15773479/faculty-position-open-rank-in-real-estate-economics</guid>
								<description>Los Angeles, California,  University of Southern California Sol Price School of Public Policy Faculty Position (Open Rank) in Real Estate Economics
 Position Description and Qualifications:
 The University of Southern California&#8217;s Sol Price School of Public Policy invites applications for a tenure-track faculty position in the area of real estate development at the Associate Professor or Professor level.
 Applicants should hold a doctoral degree and demonstrate excellent research and teaching records, appropriate to rank.&#xa0; Preference will be given to those who have research and teaching interests that readily link to the economic, social, demographic, equity and public policy issues associated with real estate development.&#xa0; The specific area of specialization is open.
 Diversity, equity, and inclusion are integral to our university&#8217;s commitment to excellence in research, engagement, and education. We encourage applications from candidates that identify with groups that are historically underrepresented in real estate development.
 The successful applicant will have a close affiliation with the highly regarded Lusk Center for Real Estate, and may be involved with its innovative Ross Minority Program in Real Estate, which provides technical training for those interested in urban redevelopment.&#xa0; Scholars affiliated with the Lusk Center collaborate with industry leaders, public decision makers, and community experts to craft innovative solutions to the day&#8217;s pressing real estate development and finance challenges.&#xa0;
 Applicants are encouraged from a broad range of disciplines (e.g., economics, business, urban planning, public policy) with a demonstrated capacity to integrate methods and insights across disciplinary boundaries.&#xa0; The School offers an undergraduate major and minor in real estate development, and a Master of Real Estate Development.&#xa0; Our new colleague will contribute to teaching in our real estate development programs at the undergraduate, masters, and doctoral levels.&#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0; The position includes the possibility of a leadership position within the newly formed Department of Real Estate.&#xa0;
 We encourage applicants as a component of their teaching and research statement, to discuss their experience or commitment to engaging with diversity through activities such as fostering an inclusive environment, working with students from diverse backgrounds, or incorporating diverse perspectives.
 About the Sol Price School of Public Policy:
 The mission of the Sol Price School of Public Policy is to improve the quality of life for people and their communities, here and abroad.&#xa0; We achieve this mission through education and research that promote innovative solutions to the most critical issues facing society, with a particular focus on governance, urban development, and social policy. The Price School offers Ph.D. programs in Public Policy and Management and in Urban Planning and Development; masters&#8217; degrees in Public Administration, Public Policy, Nonprofit Leadership and Management, Urban Planning, Health Administration, and Real Estate Development; executive masters&#8217; degrees; and an interdisciplinary undergraduate degree.&#xa0;
 Our mission statement drives all of the work of the Price School and underscores our efforts to increase the diversity of our faculty.&#xa0; The people and communities we serve locally and abroad require that we respond to the broader social and demographic shifts we see with a faculty that is representative of these shifts.
 USC is one of the world&#8217;s premiere research universities, and the Price School is a major contributor to the university&#8217;s reputation.&#xa0; Our school supports an array of thematic research centers with $80 million in active sponsored research, ranking third overall in funded research at USC on a per faculty basis. Much of the school&#8217;s research is conducted through its centers, institutes, and research groups. Among them are the Bedrosian Center on Governance, Center on Philanthropy and Public Policy, Price Center for Social Innovation, Schwarzenegger Institute for State and Global Policy, Center for Economic Development, Center for Sustainable Cities, National Center for Metropolitan Transportation Research, Lusk Center for Real Estate, Schaeffer Center for Health Policy and Economics, and the Center for Risk and Economic Analysis of Terrorism Events (CREATE), the country&#8217;s first Homeland Security Center of Excellence.
 For additional information, see our website:  www.usc.edu/schools/price/
 Compensation and Benefits:
 The University of Southern California offers a competitive salary within an academic environment based on the candidate&#8217;s experience and accomplishments. The university also offers excellent benefits to employees, which include: health, dental and life insurance; tuition assistance; disability and retirement plans; credit union membership; and participation in cultural and social events, as well as access to athletic and recreational facilities.
 &#xa0; An Equal Opportunity Employer:
 USC is an equal opportunity, affirmative action employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, protected veteran status, disability, or any other characteristic protected by law or USC policy. USC will consider for employment all qualified applicants with criminal histories in a manner consistent with the requirements of the&#xa0; Los Angeles Fair Chance Initiative for Hiring &#xa0;ordinance. We provide reasonable accommodations to applicants and employees with disabilities. Applicants with questions about access or requiring a reasonable accommodation for any part of the application or hiring process should contact USC Human Resources by phone at (213) 821-8100, or by email at&#xa0; uschr@usc.edu . Inquiries will be treated as confidential to the extent permitted by law.
 Apply for this Position:
 Applicants should submit a letter of interest, curriculum vitae and a list of three references.&#xa0; Please apply online at  https://usccareers.usc.edu/job/los-angeles/faculty-position-open-rank-in-real-estate-economics/1209/8827950096
 &#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 19:19:32 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15750640/assistant-professor-in-marketing</link>

								<title>Assistant Professor in Marketing | Wenzhou-Kean University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15750640/assistant-professor-in-marketing</guid>
								<description>Wenzhou, China,  Wenzhou-Kean University
 &#xa0;
 Assistant Professor in Marketing
 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;
 Along with NYU Shanghai and Duke University Kunshan, Wenzhou-Kean University (WKU) is one of only three full legal-person Sino-American universities approved by the Ministry of Education in China. We invite applications for one full-time tenure track position at the rank of Assistant Professor in Marketing to begin in  Fall or Spring 2022 . Ability to demonstrate quality teaching is a must.&#xa0; The successful candidate will be able to teach courses such as Marketing Research and Consumer Behavior, as well as participate in the full range of faculty responsibilities, including scholarly research and service to the University. Applicants should possess an earned doctorate in Marketing from an AACSB accredited program, or anticipate completion by July 2022. Applicants with terminal Social Science degrees from top universities and proven research records in Marketing are also strongly encouraged to apply. To receive full consideration by the search committee, candidates need to submit a cover letter, CV, research statement, unofficial transcripts and contact information for three references by email to: Search Committee Chairperson at  wkucbpm@wku.edu.cn  . Official transcripts for terminal degrees and three current letters of recommendation are required before appointment.&#xa0;
 &#xa0;
 A branch campus of Kean University (USA), WKU sits on over 500 beautiful acres with a brand new state-of-the-art business building (http://www.wku.edu.cn/en/cbpm/). All instruction is in English and all curricula are provided by Kean USA, a comprehensive New Jersey state university located just 30 minutes from downtown New York City. A city of 9 million people, Wenzhou is only one hour by plane and just over three hours by high-speed train from Shanghai and Hong Kong.
 &#xa0;
 Business faculty positions at WKU offer:

 Extremely competitive salaries that are multi-year Tax-Free for citizens of countries such as U.S.A.
 Generous home leave, housing, schooling, and relocation allowances, as well as 8% front-load retirement benefits with immediate vesting.
 Research funding
 A collegial environment
 The opportunity to teach high quality students with more than half of them go the graduate schools at Top 50 Universities in the world.

 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;
 Wenzhou-Kean University is an Equal Opportunity Employer
 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 01:47:02 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15750638/assistant-associate-full-professor-in-management</link>

								<title>Assistant/Associate/Full Professor in Management | Wenzhou-Kean University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15750638/assistant-associate-full-professor-in-management</guid>
								<description>Wenzhou, China,  Wenzhou-Kean University
 Assistant/Associate/Full  Professor in Management
 Along with NYU Shanghai and Duke University Kunshan, Wenzhou-Kean University (WKU) is one of only three full legal-person Sino-American universities with all English instruction approved by the Ministry of Education in China. We invite research-oriented applicants for full-time tenure track positions at the rank of Assistant or Associate Professor in Management to begin in  Spring or Fall 2022 . High research candidates with UTD ( https://jindal.utdallas.edu/the-utd-top-100-business-school-research-rankings/list-of-journals ) publication record may be considered for a special research track with 1-1 or 2-0 load, generous research funding, up to RMB 1 million (about USD $150K) in 10-month tax-FREE salary (pending nationality), and additional allowance besides standard benefit package, e.g. extra RMB one million in housing subsidy.
 &#xa0;
 Applicants should possess an earned doctorate in Management &#8211; preferred in the fields of Operations, Supply Chain, or Business Analytics &#8211; from an AACSB or EQUIS accredited program, or anticipate completion by August 2022. Applicants with terminal related Social Science degrees from Ivy League or better schools are also strongly encouraged to apply. To receive full consideration by the search committee, candidates need to submit a cover letter, CV, research statement, unofficial transcripts and contact information for three references by email to: Search Committee Chairperson at  wkucbpm@wku.edu.cn  . Official transcripts for terminal degrees and three current letters of recommendation are required before appointment.&#xa0;
 &#xa0;
 WKU sits on over 500 beautiful acres with new state-of-the-art facility (http://www.wku.edu.cn/en/cbpm/). A city of 9 million people, Wenzhou is only one hour by plane and just over three hours by high-speed train from Shanghai and Hong Kong.
 Business faculty positions at WKU offer:

 Highly competitive salaries that are multi-year Tax-Free for citizens of countries such as U.S.A.
 Generous home leave, housing, schooling, and relocation allowances, as well as 8% front-load retirement benefits with immediate vesting.
 Research funding
 A collegial environment
 The opportunity to teach high quality students with half of them go to the graduate schools at Top 50 Universities in the world.

 &#xa0;
 Wenzhou-Kean University is an Equal Opportunity Employer
 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 01:47:31 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15767510/assistant-associate-professor-of-management-strategy-or-entrepreneurship</link>

								<title>Assistant/Associate Professor of Management &#8211; Strategy or Entrepreneurship | University of Connecticut</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15767510/assistant-associate-professor-of-management-strategy-or-entrepreneurship</guid>
								<description>Storrs, Connecticut,  INTRODUCTION
 The Management Department in the School of Business at the University of Connecticut invites applications for a tenure-track position at the rank of Assistant or Associate Professor to begin in Fall 2022.
 The successful candidate will be expected to share a deep commitment to publishing high quality research in premier management journals, to effective instruction at the undergraduate and graduate levels, to the development of innovative courses, and to the mentoring of students in their professional development. In addition, individuals will be expected to contribute to scholarship and outreach targeted at the professional community so as to maintain faculty qualifications under AACSB guidelines.&#xa0; Successful candidates will also be expected to assist the University in its efforts to broaden participation among members of under-represented groups; demonstrate through their research, teaching, and/or public engagement the richness of diversity in the learning experience; integrate multicultural experiences into relevant course content; contribute to the development of pedagogical techniques designed to meet the needs of diverse learning styles and intellectual interests.
 The faculty of the UConn Management Department are a group of scholars, teachers, and people that find professional and personal fulfillment in working with each other and making a difference through research, working with students, and engaging the business community.&#xa0; Our small size (11 tenure-track, 5 non-tenure in-residence) makes for a cohesive yet multidisciplinary program with collaborative efforts across management areas. Our per capita research productivity in premier journals (e.g., Academy of Management Journal, Academy of Management Review, Journal of Applied Psychology, Strategic Management Journal, Organizational Science, Management Science, and Journal of Management) ranks among the top management departments worldwide. The Department of Management is the academic home of entrepreneurship offering undergraduate and MBA concentrations and minors in connection with the Schools of Engineering and Nursing. This position will support the growth of our research and teaching capabilities in the discipline following the success of our Innovation Quest Program, the Connecticut Center for Entrepreneurship and Innovation, and the newly created Peter J. Werth Institute for Entrepreneurship, created after a transformational gift of $22.5 million in 2018.
 Founded in 1881, UConn is a Land Grant and Sea Grant institution and member of the Space Grant Consortium. It is the state&#8217;s flagship institution of higher education and includes a main campus in Storrs, CT, four regional campuses throughout the state, and 13 Schools and Colleges, including a Law School in Hartford, and Medical and Dental Schools at the UConn Health campus in Farmington. The University has approximately 10,000 faculty and staff and 32,000 students, including nearly 24,000 undergraduates and over 8,000 graduate and professional students. UConn is a Carnegie Foundation R1 (highest research activity) institution, among the top 25 public universities in the nation. Through research, teaching, service, and outreach, UConn embraces diversity and cultivates leadership, integrity, and engaged citizenship in its students, faculty, staff, and alumni. UConn promotes the health and well-being of citizens by enhancing the social, economic, cultural, and natural environments of the state and beyond. The University serves as a beacon of academic and research excellence as well as a center for innovation and social service to communities. UConn is a leader in many scholarly, research, and innovation areas. Today, the path forward includes exciting opportunities and notable challenges. Record numbers of undergraduate applications and support for student success have enabled the University to become extraordinarily selective.
 MINIMUM QUALIFICATIONS

 For Assistant Professor Rank:&#xa0; Completed Ph.D. in management or related field, or expected by August 22, 2022. Equivalent foreign degrees are acceptable.
 For Associate Professor Rank:&#xa0; Completed Ph.D. in management or related field and a record of scholarly productivity (with developing national reputation) that would support appointment to the rank of tenured Associate Professor of Management.
 Publications, or potential to publish, in premier management journals.
 Demonstrated teaching excellence in higher education.
 A deep commitment to promoting diversity through their academic and research programs.
 Excellent interpersonal skills and demonstrated collegiality.

 PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS&#xa0;

 Evidence of pipeline for excellence in Entrepreneurship research.
 Experience in undergraduate and MBA teaching.
 Ability to contribute through research, teaching and/or service, and community engagement to the diversity and excellence of the Department&#8217;s mission.
 Demonstrated interest in training doctoral students.
 Experience mentoring students from all academic disciplines who are interested in entrepreneurship as a career alternative.
 Experience with entrepreneurial start-ups/ventures.

 APPOINTMENT TERMS
 The position is a full-time, nine-month appointment that will be located primarily at the Storrs campus with the possibility of work at UConn&#8217;s regional campuses across the state or online.&#xa0; Salary will be commensurate with qualifications and experience.
 TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF EMPLOYMENT
 Employment at the University of Connecticut is contingent upon the successful candidate&#8217;s compliance with the  University&#8217;s Mandatory Workforce COVID-19 Vaccination Policy .&#xa0; This Policy states that all workforce members are required to have or obtain a Covid-19 vaccination as a term and condition of employment at UConn, unless an exemption or deferral has been approved.&#xa0;
 Employment of the successful candidate is contingent upon the successful completion of a pre-employment criminal background check.
 TO APPLY
 Please apply online to Academic Jobs Online&#xa0; https://academicjobsonline.org/ajo/jobs/20454  and submit the following application materials:

 A  cover letter  specifically addressing credentials relative to the minimum and preferred qualifications listed above.
 Curriculum vitae
 A one-page  teaching statement  with attached  teaching evaluations .
 A one-page  research and scholarship statement  (innovative concepts that will form the basis of academic career, experience in proposal development, mentorship of graduate students, etc.)
 A one-page  commitment to diversity statement  (as related to broadening participation, integrating multicultural experiences in instruction and research and pedagogical techniques to meet the needs of diverse learning styles, etc.)
 Sample  journal articles or books
 Three letters of reference .&#xa0;

 Evaluation of applicants will begin immediately and continue until the position is filled.&#xa0; Preference will be given to applications received by November 19, 2021.&#xa0;&#xa0;
 For more information regarding the Department of Management, please visit the department website at  http://management.business.uconn.edu/ .&#xa0;
 Inquiries other than applications can be directed to:&#xa0;
 Pamela Costa Management Department University of Connecticut School of Business 2100 Hillside Road, Unit 1041A Storrs, CT 06269-1041 pamela.costa@uconn.edu
 This position will be filled subject to budgetary approval.
 All employees are subject to adherence to the State Code of Ethics, which may be found at&#xa0; http://www.ct.gov/ethics/site/default.asp .
 The University of Connecticut is committed to building and supporting a multicultural and diverse community of students, faculty and staff. The diversity of students, faculty and staff continues to increase, as does the number of honors students, valedictorians and salutatorians who consistently make UConn their top choice. More than 100 research centers and institutes serve the University&#8217;s teaching, research, diversity, and outreach missions, leading to UConn&#8217;s ranking as one of the nation&#8217;s top research universities. UConn&#8217;s faculty and staff are the critical link to fostering and expanding our vibrant, multicultural and diverse University community. As an Affirmative Action/Equal Employment Opportunity employer, UConn encourages applications from women, veterans, people with disabilities and members of traditionally underrepresented populations.
 &#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 15:48:04 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15750219/business-organizations-and-society-tenure-track-assistant-professor</link>

								<title>Business, Organizations and Society, Tenure Track &#8211; Assistant Professor&#xa0; | New York University Abu Dhabi</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15750219/business-organizations-and-society-tenure-track-assistant-professor</guid>
								<description>Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates,  Business, Organizations and Society&#xa0; Tenure Track &#8211; Assistant Professor &#xa0; Division of Social Science&#xa0; NYU Abu Dhabi&#xa0; Position Description The Division of Social Science at NYU Abu Dhabi (NYUAD) is searching for new faculty to conduct innovative research and educate the next generation of global leaders. You are invited to apply for a tenure-track, Assistant Professor faculty position in a new undergraduate program, a B.A. in Business, Organizations and Society. The program is interdisciplinary and focuses on the role and impact of business within society. Established on principles of the liberal arts, the program integrates business theory and application, and prepares students to take on roles in businesses and effectively and holistically examine the implications of business decisions for society from multiple perspectives (i.e., social, political, economic, and cultural).&#xa0; The program seeks applicants whose research and teaching are rooted in management, organizational studies or a related area. Applicants should provide a strong record of scholarship, and evidence of potential to develop and lead high-quality research, with national and international significance. Applicants should demonstrate an outstanding track record for their career stage, in both research and teaching. The successful candidate will be expected to develop and maintain a cutting edge, innovative, and highly visible research program; participate in student advising and mentorship; teach graduate and/or undergraduate courses in the area of management, entrepreneurship, social impact, and business analytics; or develop new courses in their area of expertise, as appropriate.&#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0; The interdisciplinary composition and expertise within the Division of Social Science, as well as the Business, Organizations and Society program, will be used to expand research activities on how businesses influence and are influenced by the societies, political systems, and economies in which they operate. There are many collaboration opportunities within NYUAD, which already houses a number of interdisciplinary research centers and labs, including the Center for Behavioral Institutional Design (C-BID), Center for Interacting Urban Networks (CITIES), and Social Science Experimental Lab (SSEL). NYUAD values diversity, inclusion, belonging, and equity; such principles are fundamental to the university commitment to excellence.&#xa0; NYUAD students come from more than 115 countries, with no single one nationality exceeding more than 15 percent of the total student population. Likewise, our faculty are highly diverse and community minded: our modern campus is home to over 320 faculty who represent more than 45 different nationalities, all of whom bring a global perspective to their classrooms and research projects. Our faculty are the engines that sustain our inclusive environment. Research is advanced by over 400 highly qualified research staff, who are likewise drawn from all over the world.&#xa0;We particularly welcome applications from female scholars as well as members of traditionally underrepresented groups. About NYU Abu Dhabi Established in partnership between New York University (NYU) and the emirate of Abu Dhabi, NYU Abu Dhabi (NYUAD) has assembled over the past decade a remarkable community of scholars, students, researchers, artists, inventors, and others who have contributed to the growth of the UAE&#8217;s capital as a global hub of knowledge and culture, while establishing a new model of higher education for today&#8217;s complex world. NYUAD is animated by inspiring, diverse faculty, students, and staff working together in an exciting and dynamic city. As an international center of excellence in teaching and research, our goal is to attract outstanding faculty who are leaders in their fields, encouraging them to create programs that draw outstanding students and providing an intellectually rich environment.&#xa0; Students are drawn from among the world&#8217;s best. They are bright, intellectually passionate, and committed to building a campus environment anchored in mutual respect, understanding, and care. The NYUAD undergraduate student body has garnered an impressive record of scholarships, graduate-school appointments, and many other global honors. Graduate education is an area of growth for the university and the current graduate student population of over 100 students is expected to expand in the next decade.&#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0; NYUAD is committed to building and strengthening a university-wide culture of inclusion, diversity, belonging, and equity (IDBE). For more information on NYUAD&#8217;s commitment to IDBE and how these values create fundamental to our mission please visit&#xa0; https://nyuad.nyu.edu/en/about/inclusion-diversity-belonging-and-equity.html Working for NYUAD A world-class institution deserves world-class benefits. At NYUAD, we recognize that Abu Dhabi is more than where you work, it&#8217;s your home. In order for faculty to thrive, we offer a comprehensive benefits package to our top talent. This starts with a generous relocation allowance to ensure a smooth transition to Abu Dhabi, followed by a competitive salary, housing, and transportation allowance; educational assistance for your dependents; access to health and wellness services, plus more. NYUAD is committed to faculty success throughout the academic career trajectory, providing support for ambitious and world class research projects and innovative, interactive teaching approaches. NYUAD supports faculty through fellowships and affiliations with research centers both at NYUAD and in the NYU network more generally. Support for dual-career families is a priority.&#xa0; Click&#xa0; here &#xa0;for more information on benefits for you and your dependents. Qualifications This position requires a Ph.D. in Management, Sociology, Psychology, Social Psychology, Economics, or a related field, and a specialization in management, organizations or a related area.&#xa0; We seek individuals who have a strong record of teaching, mentoring, and scholarship, and have the ability to develop and lead high-quality teaching and research with special attention to business, organizations, and society. Application Instructions To apply for this position, please submit the following items to:&#xa0; https://apply.interfolio.com/95473

 Curriculum Vitae
 Cover Letter
 Research Statement
 Teaching Statement
 Recent Teaching Evaluations (if available)
 Diversity Statement&#xa0;
 Three (3) Representative Writing Samples
 Three (3) letters of recommendation

 We will begin reviewing applications on December&#xa0;15th, 2021, and will continue until the position is filled. Shortlisted candidates are expected to interview in early Spring 2022. We anticipate that successful candidates can start the appointment and relocate to Abu Dhabi in the academic year 2022-2023. NYUAD is committed to equality and is an equal opportunity employer. We encourage applications from candidates who will enrich and contribute to the cultural and ethnic diversity of our University. For questions about this position, please email&#xa0; nyuad.socialscience@nyu.edu . Join NYU Abu Dhabi, an exceptional place for exceptional people. UAE Nationals are encouraged to apply. Equal Employment Opportunity Statement For people in the EU, click here for information on your privacy rights under GDPR: &#xa0; www.nyu.edu/it/gdpr NYU is an equal opportunity employer committed to equity, diversity, and social inclusion.</description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 09:28:59 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15750641/assistant-professor-in-global-business</link>

								<title>Assistant Professor in Global Business | Wenzhou-Kean University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15750641/assistant-professor-in-global-business</guid>
								<description>Wenzhou, China,  Wenzhou-Kean University
 &#xa0;
 Assistant Professor in Global Business
 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;
 Along with NYU Shanghai and Duke University Kunshan, Wenzhou-Kean University (WKU) is one of only three full legal-person Sino-American universities with all English instruction approved by the Ministry of Education in China. We invite applications for full-time positions at the rank of Assistant Professor (tenure track) in Global Business to begin in  Spring or Fall 2022 . The successful candidate will be able to teach IB and strategy related courses, as well as participate in the full range of faculty responsibilities, including scholarly research and service to the University. Applicants should possess an earned doctorate in field relevant to International Business - such as management, finance, business strategy - from an AACSB accredited program, or anticipate completion by July 2022. Applicants with terminal related Social Science degrees from Ivy League or better schools are also strongly encouraged to apply. To receive full consideration by the search committee, candidates need to submit a cover letter, CV, research statement, unofficial transcripts and contact information for three references by email to: Search Committee Chairperson at   wkucbpm@wku.edu.cn  . Official transcripts for terminal degrees and three current letters of recommendation are required before appointment.&#xa0;
 &#xa0;
 WKU sits on over 500 beautiful acres with new state-of-the-art facility (http://www.wku.edu.cn/en/cbpm/). A city of 9 million people, Wenzhou is only one hour by plane and just over three hours by high-speed train from Shanghai and Hong Kong.
 Business faculty positions at WKU offer:

 Extremely competitive salaries that are multi-year Tax-Free for citizens of countries such as U.S.A.
 Generous home leave, housing, schooling, and relocation allowances, as well as 8% front-load retirement benefits with immediate vesting.
 Research funding
 A collegial environment
 The opportunity to teach high quality students with half of them go to the graduate schools at Top 50 Universities in the world.

 &#xa0;
 Wenzhou-Kean University is an Equal Opportunity Employer
 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 01:46:46 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15767519/assistant-professor-in-residence-department-of-management</link>

								<title>Assistant Professor In-Residence, Department of Management | University of Connecticut</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15767519/assistant-professor-in-residence-department-of-management</guid>
								<description>Storrs, Connecticut,  INTRODUCTION
 The Management Department in the School of Business at the University of Connecticut invites applications for a non-tenure track position at the rank of Assistant Professor In-Residence to begin in Fall 2022.&#xa0;This position involves teaching courses primarily in the areas of entrepreneurship/management at the undergraduate and graduate levels, with the ability to teach other management courses in the areas of strategy, international business, organizational behavior, or human resources.&#xa0; Additionally, the position involves publishing research in academic or quality practitioner outlets, teaching-oriented journals, and/or scholarly books.&#xa0; There is also the expectation of participation in service activities within the Management Department, the School and the University, as well as outreach to the business community.
 The successful candidate will be expected to share a deep commitment to effective instruction at the undergraduate and graduate levels, to the development of innovative courses, and to the mentoring of students in their professional development.&#xa0; In addition, individuals will be expected to contribute to scholarship and outreach targeted at the professional community so as to maintain faculty qualifications under AACSB guidelines.&#xa0; Successful candidates will share a deep commitment to effective instruction and will be expected to assist the University in its efforts to broaden participation among members of under-represented groups; demonstrate through their research, teaching, and/or public engagement the richness of diversity in the learning experience; integrate multicultural experiences into relevant course content; contribute to the development of pedagogical techniques designed to meet the needs of diverse learning styles and intellectual interests.
 Founded in 1881, UConn is a Land Grant and Sea Grant institution and member of the Space Grant Consortium. It is the state&#8217;s flagship institution of higher education and includes a main campus in Storrs, CT, four regional campuses throughout the state, and 13 Schools and Colleges, including a Law School in Hartford, and Medical and Dental Schools at the UConn Health campus in Farmington. The University has approximately 10,000 faculty and staff and 32,000 students, including nearly 24,000 undergraduates and over 8,000 graduate and professional students. UConn is a Carnegie Foundation R1 (highest research activity) institution, among the top 25 public universities in the nation. Through research, teaching, service, and outreach, UConn embraces diversity and cultivates leadership, integrity, and engaged citizenship in its students, faculty, staff, and alumni. UConn promotes the health and well-being of citizens by enhancing the social, economic, cultural, and natural environments of the state and beyond. The University serves as a beacon of academic and research excellence as well as a center for innovation and social service to communities. UConn is a leader in many scholarly, research, and innovation areas. Today, the path forward includes exciting opportunities and notable challenges. Record numbers of undergraduate applications and support for student success have enabled the University to become extraordinarily selective.
 MINIMUM QUALIFICATIONS&#xa0;

 Completed Ph.D. in Management or related field, or expected by August 23, 2022. Equivalent foreign degrees are acceptable.
 Expertise in the field of Entrepreneurship.
 Demonstrated teaching excellence in higher education.
 Demonstrated ability to supervise students in learning projects.
 Excellent interpersonal skills and demonstrated collegiality.

 PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS&#xa0;

 Earned Ph.D. from an AACSB-accredited institution.
 Taught corporate entrepreneurship, social entrepreneurship, and lean start-up.
 A demonstrated publication record.
 Experience in undergraduate and MBA teaching.
 Ability to contribute through research, teaching and/or service and community engagement to the diversity and excellence of the Department&#8217;s mission.

 APPOINTMENT TERMS&#xa0;
 This is a full-time, 9-month end-date non-tenure track position with the possibility of annual reappointment, contingent upon positive annual reviews and program funding, and may lead to a multi-year appointment.&#xa0; The successful candidate will be assigned a primary academic appointment at the Storrs campus, with the possibility of course assignment outside of the base campus or online.&#xa0; Salary will be commensurate with qualifications and experience.
 TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF EMPLOYMENT
 Employment at the University of Connecticut is contingent upon the successful candidate&#8217;s compliance with the  University&#8217;s Mandatory Workforce COVID-19 Vaccination Policy .&#xa0; This Policy states that all workforce members are required to have or obtain a Covid-19 vaccination as a term and condition of employment at UConn, unless an exemption or deferral has been approved.&#xa0;
 Employment of the successful candidate is contingent upon the successful completion of a pre-employment criminal background check.
 TO APPLY&#xa0;
 Please apply online to Academic Jobs Online&#xa0; https://academicjobsonline.org/ajo/jobs/20452  and submit the following application materials:

 A  cover letter  specifically addressing your credentials relative to the minimum and preferred qualifications listed above.
 Curriculum vitae
 A one-page  teaching statement  with attached teaching evaluations.
 A one-page  research and scholarship statement  (innovative concepts that will form the basis of academic career, experience in proposal development, mentorship of graduate students, etc.)
 A one-page  commitment to diversity statement  (as related to broadening participation, integrating multicultural experiences in instruction and research and pedagogical techniques to meet the needs of diverse learning styles, etc.)
 Three letters of reference

 Evaluation of applicants will begin immediately and continue until the position is filled.&#xa0; Preference will be given to applications received by November 19, 2021.&#xa0;
 At the University of Connecticut, our commitment to excellence is complemented by our commitment to building a culturally diverse community.
 For more information regarding the Department of Management, please visit the department website at  http://management.business.uconn.edu/ .&#xa0;
 Inquiries other than applications can be directed to:&#xa0;
 Pamela Costa
 Management Department
 University of Connecticut
 School of Business
 2100 Hillside Road, Unit 1041A
 Storrs, CT
 06269-1041
 pamela.costa@business.uconn.edu
 This position will be filled subject the budgetary approval.
 All employees are subject to adherence to the State Code of Ethics which may be found at  http://www.ct.gov/ethics/site/default.asp .
 The University of Connecticut is committed to building and supporting a multicultural and diverse community of students, faculty and staff. The diversity of students, faculty and staff continues to increase, as does the number of honors students, valedictorians and salutatorians who consistently make UConn their top choice. More than 100 research centers and institutes serve the University&#8217;s teaching, research, diversity, and outreach missions, leading to UConn&#8217;s ranking as one of the nation&#8217;s top research universities. UConn&#8217;s faculty and staff are the critical link to fostering and expanding our vibrant, multicultural and diverse University community. As an Affirmative Action/Equal Employment Opportunity employer, UConn encourages applications from women, veterans, people with disabilities and members of traditionally underrepresented populations.</description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 15:53:09 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15749719/open-rank-position-in-organizational-leadership</link>

								<title>Open Rank Position in Organizational Leadership | Dalhousie University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15749719/open-rank-position-in-organizational-leadership</guid>
								<description>Halifax, Nova Scotia, Canada,  Rowe School of Business
 Open Rank Position in Organizational Leadership
 The Rowe School of Business (RSB) invites applications for a probationary tenure-track, tenure-track, or tenured 100% FTE appointment in Organizational Leadership at the rank of Lecturer, Assistant, Associate, or full Professor (dependent upon qualifications and experience) commencing July 1, 2022 (negotiable). The successful applicant will be expected to engage in leading-edge research with faculty and students, to apply for external grants, to teach, and to contribute to the academic life of the School through committee service and other activities.
 Required qualifications:

 PhD from an accredited program in a relevant discipline. Applicants very close to their thesis defense date may also be considered.
 Evidence of teaching effectiveness and experience.
 Clearly defined research agenda with established record of publication or promising track record in leadership areas such as inclusive leadership, discursive leadership, complexity leadership, Africentric leadership, Indigenous leadership, collective leadership, or critical approaches to leadership.
 Demonstrated potential for making significant contributions to our MBA program by teaching organizational leadership from the standpoint of inclusion, collaboration, and relationship management.

 Preferred qualifications, experience, and skills:

 Research focus in Africentric and Indigenous approaches to organizational leadership, such as Ubuntu and Etuaptmumk (Two-Eyed Seeing) perspectives.
 Ability to collaborate with colleagues in the school&#8217;s research clusters: healthcare, innovation, behavioural analytics, and responsible organizations.
 Demonstrated ability to collaborate and co-create curriculum to foster safer spaces for equity-seeking groups.
 Record of service positions that contribute to and reinforce a unit.

 The Management Area Group in the RSB is home to faculty members who come together with diverse methodological and disciplinary expertise, publishing in top-tier and diversity-focused journals (such as  Journal of Management; Administrative Science Quarterly; Equality, Diversity, and Inclusion: An International Journal; Business and Society; Journal of Business Ethics; Journal of Occupational Health Psychology; Harvard Business Review ). Our research positively impacts industry and our communities through applied publications, applied research, and research collaborations with the public sector, healthcare, and the military.
 The Rowe School of Business is housed in Dalhousie University&#8217;s Faculty of Management.&#xa0;We offer life-changing management education in a diverse and inclusive community that inspires social and economic innovation and responsible action, with a focus on the United Nations sustainable development goals. We are a leader in innovative, experiential learning and conduct research with lasting impact.&#xa0; Our vision is a world where talented people from the private, public, and not-for-profit sectors work together to create social and economic value and we embrace a culture of collaboration and connection.&#xa0;
 The RSB is an AACSB-accredited school with a strong research culture and a member of EFMD and EFMD Global Network. It serves over 1800 students and prides itself on developing the next generation of innovative leaders. It specializes in experiential learning including residencies, consulting projects, co-op work terms, internships, and new venture creation. Collaboration with our employer partners from around the globe brings opportunity to our students and relevancy to our programs (the Bachelor of Commerce Co-op, Bachelor of Management, Corporate Residency MBA, Blended/Online MBA in Financial Services or Leadership, Executive Education, and MSc. in Business).
 Dalhousie University is one of Canada&#8217;s leading teaching and research universities. It is a member of the U15 (a collective of some of Canada&#8217;s most research-intensive universities).&#xa0;Dalhousie&#8217;s mission is to lift the intellectual, social, and economic vitality of our local, national, and global communities through an institution-wide commitment to a world-class student experience, interdisciplinary collaboration, and mutual respect and inclusion in all aspects of our academic, research, and civic priorities. Dalhousie&#8217;s Third Century Promise, or Si&#8217;st Kasqimtlnaqnipunqekl Teli L&#8217;wi&#8217;tmasimk in Mi&#8217;kmaq, includes &#8220;Inclusive Excellence&#8221; as a strategic priority and one that we embrace in the Faculty of Management through a Strategic Plan Pillar of &#8220;Support Inclusion and Reconciliation&#8221;. More than words of a strategic plan, we are taking steps to diversify our curriculum, increase inclusion of students and faculty, and address systemic inequities.
 Dalhousie University is in Halifax, Nova Scotia, Canada. Halifax is a vibrant coastal capital city and is the business, academic, and medical centre for Canada&#8217;s east coast. It offers a high quality of life with various indoor and outdoor recreation opportunities in and near the city and rich arts and cultural institutions, including an excellent library system and plans for a new art gallery.
 Information about the Rowe School of Business and its programs may be found at  http://www.dal.ca/faculty/management/rsb.html
 All qualified candidates are encouraged to apply; however, Canadians and permanent residents will be given priority. Dalhousie University is committed to fostering a collegial culture grounded in diversity and inclusiveness. The university encourages applications from Indigenous persons, persons with a disability, racially visible persons, women, persons of minority sexual orientations and/or gender identity, and all candidates who would contribute to the diversity of our community. For more information, please visit  www.dal.ca/hiringfordiversity .
 Applicants should prepare and submit the following information within our online application system:

 Cover Letter
 Recent CV
 Research Statement  (one (1) page, reflective of your substantive research focus and the methodological approaches that you use to address your research).
 Teaching Statement  (one (1) page, reflective of your teaching philosophy and teaching interests).
 Evidence of teaching effectiveness   and experience  such as teaching evaluations, letters from colleagues or students, and/or research related to the scholarship of teaching and learning.
 Commitment to diversity and equity statement   (upload as &#8220;Portfolio&#8221;)  (one (1) page, reflective of your perspectives on broadening participation, integrating multicultural experiences in pedagogical techniques/instruction and research to meet the needs of diverse constituents).
 List of references : Names and contact information of three (3) persons. Reference letters are not required at this stage.

 Applications must be submitted electronically at  https://dal.peopleadmin.ca/postings/7686
 Review of applications will begin November 22, 2021 and continue until the position is filled. Questions regarding the position may be sent to Dr. Dana Kabat-Farr, Chair of the Search Committee at: kabatfarr@dal.ca
 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 08:29:51 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15726067/assistant-professor-in-finance</link>

								<title>Assistant Professor in Finance | Dickinson College</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15726067/assistant-professor-in-finance</guid>
								<description>Carlisle, Pennsylvania,  The Department of International Business and Management (INBM) at Dickinson College seeks a candidate to fill a tenure-track assistant professor of finance position starting in autumn semester 2022.&#xa0;
 Dickinson is a highly selective four-year liberal arts college with 2300 students. The campus is in Carlisle, PA, a 20-minute drive west of the state capitol Harrisburg and a two-hour drive from Baltimore, Washington DC and Philadelphia.&#xa0;
 The INBM Department has a distinctive curriculum that draws upon and contributes to Dickinson&#8217;s core competencies in global education, interdisciplinary studies, sustainability, and community engagement.&#xa0; Each year, roughly ten percent of the senior class graduate with a major in INBM, making it the College&#8217;s most popular program.
 The successful candidate will handle a five-course teaching load each academic year. Each year, the candidate will be asked to share responsibility for teaching the 200-level core course Finance; and to teach at least one elective business-related course based on his/her own research and teaching interest.&#xa0; From year to year, the candidate will also be asked to teach either the 100-level core course Fundamentals of Business or the 400-level Senior Seminar in International Business Strategy based on the need of the department. Starting in the second year of employment, the candidate will be expected to advise students and to engage in other forms of service to the Department and the College.&#xa0;&#xa0; Candidates must either currently hold or be on track to earn a doctorate or other terminal degree by autumn 2022 in the field of finance, who can fulfil the above-mentioned teaching obligations.
 The College is committed to building an inclusive and diverse faculty, administrative staff, and student body. Thus, we in the Department encourage applications from all qualified candidates.&#xa0;&#xa0; Given the commitment of the College, the successful candidate must have the ability to create inclusive learning environments for an increasingly diverse student body.
 Candidates should provide a letter of application that includes a statement about teaching philosophy and research interests; a curriculum vitae; a graduate transcript; three letters of recommendation, and for those with teaching experience, sample syllabi and teaching evaluations.
 Interested candidates should apply for this position electronically by January 15, 2022, via QUEST (online application system) at  https://jobs.dickinson.edu . &#xa0;Meanwhile, applications will be reviewed as they are received.&#xa0; During the review process, Department members will interview those applicants who appear to be a good fit for the position via Zoom-based conference call.&#xa0;
 The Department will invite the three finalist candidates to visit campus in February 2022 to meet Department members and Senior Administrators, provide a research talk, and offer a lecture to students.</description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 15:23:50 -0400</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15750079/dean-of-eccles-school-of-business</link>

								<title>Dean of Eccles School of Business | University of Utah</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15750079/dean-of-eccles-school-of-business</guid>
								<description>Salt Lake City, Utah,  University of Utah Dean of Eccles School of Business
 The David Eccles School of Business at The University of Utah (the U) is located at the heart of a vibrant and growing business community in Salt Lake City, Utah. With a mission that resonates across and beyond the University, the Eccles School of Business is poised to thrive in an evolving marketplace that puts a premium on entrepreneurial approaches, continuous curiosity, empathetic global citizenship and impact on the world. To secure the success of the enterprise and all members of the community, the Eccles School seeks a dean to lead the School into a bright and promising future.
 The University of Utah was founded in 1850, and its main campus is located in Salt Lake City on the foothills of the Wasatch Mountains, neighboring seven world-class ski resorts. It&#39;s Utah and international campuses serve more than 33,000 students from across the U.S. and around the world. With more than 90 major subjects at the undergraduate level and more than 100 major fields of study at the graduate level, the university prepares students to live and compete in the global workplace. The U, with its emphasis on sustainability and environmental responsibility, encourages an active, holistic lifestyle and collaborative thinking to engage students, faculty and business leaders.
 The Carnegie Foundation classifies The University of Utah as an R1: Doctoral University-Very High Research Institution. In 2019, The University of Utah was invited to join the prestigious Association of American Universities, which requires its member institutions to engage at the highest levels of research, scholarship and education. Notably, in fiscal year 2020, the university obtained a historic high of $603 million in research funding, which benefits higher education, the state of Utah and society as a whole by creating new knowledge, jobs and patents. In 2017, the Milken Institute recognized The U as No. 1 in its Best Universities for Technology Transfer listing. The U is also a member of the Pac-12 Conference.
 With multiple centers of distinction, that give students the opportunity to make their impact on the world in fields like strategic leadership, impact investing, ethics, entrepreneurship and public policy. Situated within a Salt Lake City business environment that prizes innovation, the Eccles School possesses many of the resources and attributes that characterize the successful business school of the future. Add to that students, faculty and staff who are passionate about diversity, equity, and inclusion and the education of the whole person, and you have an environment ripe for leadership that will accelerate the Eccles School into a new era of success.
 Succeeding in this era of opportunity and change requires a dean who is deeply committed to the University&#8217;s and the School&#8217;s mission and values. An earned terminal degree is required, and a track record of teaching, research and service meriting an appointment to the Eccles School&#8217;s tenured faculty is highly preferred. While candidates with meaningful academic experience are preferred, candidates with substantial knowledge of higher education who have demonstrated success in one or more enterprises outside of higher education also will be considered. Of critical need are superior communication and relationship-building skills, outstanding fiscal and budgetary ability and change management experience. Additional information about this position, including a leadership profile can be found at  www.wittkieffer.com .
 Inquiries, nominations and applications are invited. The search process is currently underway and will continue until the position is filled. Application materials should be submitted using WittKieffer&#8217;s  candidate portal . Nominations and inquiries can be directed to Mercedes Vance, Alejandra Gillette-Teran and Natalie Song at  UtahBusinessDean@wittkieffer.com
 The University of Utah values diversity and is committed to equal opportunity for all persons regardless of age, color, disability, ethnicity, marital status, national origin, race, religion, sex, sexual orientation, veteran status or any other status protected by law.
 &#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 12:51:38 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15726045/assistant-professor-in-international-business</link>

								<title>Assistant Professor in International Business | Dickinson College</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15726045/assistant-professor-in-international-business</guid>
								<description>Carlisle, Pennsylvania,  The Department of International Business and Management (INBM) at Dickinson College seeks a candidate to fill a tenure-track assistant professor of international business position starting in autumn semester 2022.&#xa0;
 Dickinson is a highly selective four-year liberal arts college with 2300 students. The campus is in Carlisle, PA, a 20-minute drive west of the state capitol Harrisburg and a two-hour drive from Baltimore, Washington DC and Philadelphia.&#xa0;
 The INBM Department has a distinctive curriculum that draws upon and contributes to Dickinson&#8217;s core competencies in global education, interdisciplinary studies, sustainability, and community engagement.&#xa0; Each year, roughly ten percent of the senior class graduate with a major in INBM, making it the College&#8217;s most popular program.
 The successful candidate will handle a five-course teaching load each academic year.&#xa0; Each year, the candidate will be asked to share responsibility for teaching the 200-level core course Global Business: Theory and Context; and to teach at least one elective business-related course based on his/her own research and teaching interest.&#xa0; From year to year, the candidate will also be asked to teach either the 100-level core course Fundamentals of Business or the 400-level Senior Seminar in International Business Strategy based on the need of the department. Starting in the second year of employment, the candidate will be expected to advise students and to engage in other forms of service to the Department and the College. &#xa0;&#xa0; Candidates must either currently hold or be on track to earn a doctorate or other terminal degree by autumn 2022 in the fields of international business, international management, or related areas who can fulfil the above-mentioned teaching obligations.
 The College is committed to building an inclusive and diverse faculty, administrative staff, and student body. Thus, we in the Department encourage applications from all qualified candidates.&#xa0;&#xa0; Given the commitment of the College, the successful candidate must have the ability to create inclusive learning environments for an increasingly diverse student body.
 Candidates should provide a letter of application that includes a statement about teaching philosophy and research interests; a curriculum vitae; a graduate transcript; three letters of recommendation, and for those with teaching experience, sample syllabi and teaching evaluations.
 Interested candidates should apply for this position electronically by January 15, 2022, via QUEST (online application system) at  https://jobs.dickinson.edu . &#xa0;Meanwhile, applications will be reviewed as they are received.&#xa0; During the review process, Department members will interview those applicants who appear to be a good fit for the position via Zoom-based conference call.&#xa0;
 The Department will invite the three finalist candidates to visit campus in February 2022 to meet Department members and Senior Administrators, provide a research talk, and offer a lecture to students.</description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 15:12:48 -0400</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15749990/assistant-professor-tenure-track-sports-management</link>

								<title>Assistant Professor Tenure Track Sports Management | St. Bonaventure University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15749990/assistant-professor-tenure-track-sports-management</guid>
								<description>St. Bonaventure, New York,  St. Bonaventure University invites applications for a tenure-track position in sports management at the Assistant/Associate Professor level, housed within the School of Business. St. Bonaventure University emphasizes teaching and is looking for candidates who are excited about being a part of our student learning-focused mission. Candidates must be committed to excellent teaching, engaging in research related to the business aspects of sport, working collegially with fellow faculty, and further, cultivate sports management partnerships. Candidate must be able to create sports management experiential learning opportunities for students in and out of the classroom. &#xa0;Candidates should possess expertise in two or more of the following areas; sport finance, sport economics, sport sales, sport marketing, international sport business, sport governance, sport leadership, E-sports, event/facilities management and/or other sport business related courses. &#xa0; The candidate must be willing to teach in both on-line and in-person, undergraduate and graduate.&#xa0;&#xa0;
 Examples of Duties

 Teach graduate and undergraduate courses (12 credits each semester). B. Serve as an advisor for undergraduate majors; and C. Participate in service activities for the department, the division, the college, industry, and/or the community as needed. Faculty are expected to engage in the following activities, where appropriate, as part of their normal services:
 Teaching, including the preparation of course syllabi and classes, the preparation and grading of examinations, the supervision of laboratories and other practica, and the direction of theses, honor projects, and independent study work.
 Research, publication, and professional activity within one&#39;s field of specialization or otherwise directed towards the University&#39;s mission.&#xa0;
 Student advisement, with maintenance of reasonable and scheduled office hours.
 Participation in activities (usually through committee work) designed to advance the mission and quality of the University, School, and Departmental programs. Assignments to routine committee work will be made in consideration of other demands placed on the faculty member by the University.&#xa0;
 Attendance at Department, School, and general Faculty and University meetings including commencements, convocations, and other official University exercises.
 Community work outside the University.

 &#xa0; Typical Qualifications
 Ph.D. or ABD with an emphasis in sports management from an AACSB-accredited program is required or a doctoral degree in sports management accredited by COSMA with research in the area of sports business. Sports Industry experience is strongly desired but not required. Must meet the AACSB academically qualified (scholarly academic) requirement Please attached the following with your application: 1) curriculum vitae; 2) a cover letter specifically addressing the requirements in this posting; 3) statement on teaching philosophy; 4) statement on research/sample; 5) statement outlining your commitment to inclusion and diversity; and 6) name and contact information for three professional references&#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 11:51:36 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15743574/assistant-associate-professor-of-management</link>

								<title>Assistant/Associate Professor of Management | Ball State University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15743574/assistant-associate-professor-of-management</guid>
								<description>Muncie, Indiana,  Department of Management
 Assistant/Associate Professor of Management
 Ball State University
 The Department of Management has a full-time tenure track position at the rank of Assistant or Associate Professor available beginning August 2022. Primary responsibilities include teaching, conducting scholarly research, and service.&#xa0;
 At Ball State University, Inclusiveness and freedom of expression are a part of our enduring values and inform all of our efforts. We encourage applicants to familiarize themselves with our  Inclusive Excellence Plan  to learn more about our commitment and to identify how you might contribute to these efforts.
 Minimum Qualifications:  PhD in management or other closely-related field from an accredited institution of higher education by date of appointment. (ABD&#xa0;near completion will be considered, but the degree must be conferred by date of appointment.)
 Employer will consider sponsorship.
 Preferred Qualifications:  Earned doctorate from an&#xa0;AACSB-accredited institution in Management or a closely related field, expertise in the area of strategic management, leadership, and/or international management, evidence of teaching effectiveness, evidence of scholarly research or potential for scholarship, relevant industry work/business experience, demonstrated commitment to supporting diversity, equity, and inclusion.
 Apply online at:  https://bsu.peopleadmin.com/postings/27922 . Include the following documents with your application: curriculum vitae and cover letter addressed to Matt Marvel. In the Applicant Documents section of this application, please provide an inclusive excellence statement describing how you would contribute to the development of a diverse and inclusive learning community at Ball State University through your teaching, research, and/or service. Please include examples of your contributions when possible. Word limit 500.&#xa0;The option to upload transcripts is available. Original, official transcripts showing the highest related degree earned is required at the time of hire (even if obtained at BSU). Degree verification will be conducted.
 Review of applications will begin immediately and will be accepted through December 9, 2021.
 Ball State University is located in Muncie, Indiana, on an attractive campus 45 miles northeast of Indianapolis. Approximately 22,000 graduate and undergraduate students enroll in one of eight academic colleges that offer 120 undergraduate programs. We offer more than 140 master&#8217;s, doctoral, certificate, and specialist degrees, with many of them ranking among the best in the nation. We engage students in educational, research, and creative endeavors that empower our graduates to have fulfilling careers and meaningful lives enriched by lifelong learning and service, while we enhance the economic, environmental, and social vitality of our community, our state, and our world.
 The Ball State way is rooted in the Beneficence Pledge &#8211; a commitment to excellence in teaching and scholarship, honesty and integrity, social responsibility, gratitude and valuing the intrinsic worth of each member of our community. Ball State students, faculty and staff are empowered in a culture that believes in them and demands they believe in themselves. They are partners in an innovative, immersive approach to education. They are supported by living and learning facilities that enable intellectual curiosity. We graduate scholars who are changing the world, and we&#8217;ve dedicated our University to do the same.
 &#xa0;
 The university offers an excellent wellness program and extensive benefits offerings to include a generous paid time off package and paid parental leave.&#xa0; For further information regarding benefits please visit:&#xa0;
 https://cms.bsu.edu/About/AdministrativeOffices/HumanResources/Jobs/Benefits-and-Community/Faculty &#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0;
 Ball State University is an Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action employer that is strongly and actively committed to diversity within its community. Women, minorities, individuals with disabilities and protected veterans are strongly encouraged to apply. All qualified applicants will receive equal consideration for employment without regard to race, color, ethnicity, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, gender expression, national origin, age, disability, protected veteran status or any other legally protected status.
 &#xa0;
 &#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 15:39:29 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15725259/assistant-professor-of-human-resource-management-tenure-track</link>

								<title>Assistant Professor of Human Resource Management (tenure-track) | Northern Kentucky University</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15725259/assistant-professor-of-human-resource-management-tenure-track</guid>
								<description>Highland Heights, Kentucky,  The Haile College of Business at Northern Kentucky University invites applications for a tenure-track Assistant Professor of Human Resource Management position. The expected start date for the position is August 2022.
 &#xa0;
 Candidates from all research areas in Human Resource Management are welcome to apply. Current teaching needs include courses in fundamentals of HR, recruitment and selection, compensation and benefits, and human resource management strategy (capstone), in addition to other management courses. Candidates must have a Ph.D. or DBA in Human Resource Management from an AACSB-accredited program. ABDs with evidence of imminent completion of their degree will also be considered. Those holding a Ph.D. or DBA in another closely-related management field may also be considered. Expectations for the successful candidate include: Will teach at undergraduate and graduate levels in the areas of Human Resource Management; will teach both in the classroom and/or online; will have the ability to publish quality peer-reviewed academic research; a willingness to participate in engaged service; and, a commitment and sensitivity to fostering a working and learning environment which is supportive of individuals from diverse backgrounds with a team of faculty and staff that contributes to the collegiality of the department and college.
 &#xa0;</description>
								<pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 08:15:14 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15740847/3-assistant-associate-professors-in-business-ethics-business-and-society-strategic-management</link>

								<title>3 Assistant / Associate Professors in Business Ethics / Business and Society/ Strategic Management | I&#xc9;SEG School of Management</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15740847/3-assistant-associate-professors-in-business-ethics-business-and-society-strategic-management</guid>
								<description>Lille &#38; Paris , France,  In response to its continuous growth, I&#xc9;SEG School of Management invites applications for  three permanent positions  (starting September 2022) in  Strategic Management  ( one in   Lille and one in Paris ) and one in  Business Ethics/ Business &#38; Society  ( in Lille ). The selected candidates will be part of the Management &#38; Society Department. The positions will be filled at the level of assistant or associate professor (full-time).
 ABOUT THE MANAGEMENT &#38; SOCIETY DEPARTMENT
 Created in September 2020, the Management &#38; Society Department consists of over 25 full-time academic staff, including lecturers and young scholars, in the areas of Strategy, Business and Society, Organization Studies and Strategic Management. The Management &#38; Society Department offers a range of courses at different levels (Bachelor, Master, Executive education) and supports a variety of research interests and activities. The department explicitly welcomes cross-disciplinary research efforts needed to address the challenges currently faced by both for-profit and non-profit organizations, their stakeholders and the communities in which they operate.
 The Management &#38; Society Department, together with the IESEG Centre for Organizational Responsibility (ICOR -  https://icor.ieseg.fr ), operates in line with the vision of the School to be &#8220;a unique international hub empowering changemakers for a better society&#8221;. The department&#8217;s objective is to offer first class teaching and conduct great research in the domain of Management &#38; Society in a collaborative and open environment. By doing so the department and ICOR together aim to be a source of inspiration in the development of responsible and sustainable business practices, and a source of diffusion of creative knowledge and solutions.
 The School maintains an excellent network with overseas institutions for collaborative work. Current faculty members from the Management &#38; Society Department have been successful in publishing articles in top-tier refereed journals including (amongst others) the Academy of Management Review, Academy of Management Journal, Academy of Management Discoveries, Academy of Management Perspectives, Academy of Management Annals, Journal of Management Studies, Strategic Management Journal, Industrial and Corporate Change, Journal of Management Inquiry, Organization Science, Organization Studies, Business Ethics Quarterly, Business &#38; Society, Journal of Business Ethics, Organization &#38; Environment, Long Range Planning, and California Management Review.&#xa0; ABOUT THE POSITIONS IN STRATEGIC MANAGEMENT
 Our selected applicants will be offered to teach courses in strategic management/strategy at the undergraduate, graduate and/or postgraduate level and also to contribute to the design and development of the School&#8217;s programs.
 Please submit your application here:  https://recruitment.ieseg.fr/jobs/1426217-2-assistant-associate-professor-positions-in-strategic-management?promotion=303942-trackable-share-link-aom &#xa0; &#xa0;
 ABOUT THE POSITION IN BUSINESS ETHICS/ BUSINESS &#38; SOCIETY
 Our selected applicant will be offered to teach courses in Business Ethics and Corporate Social Responsibility/Sustainability at the undergraduate, graduate and/or postgraduate level and to actively contribute to the design and development of the School&#8217;s programs.
 The selected applicant is also expected to contribute to the development of ICOR, in line with the ambitions of the School, which aims at supporting the development of responsible, innovative and enlightened organizations and managers via impactful research efforts and expertise sharing.&#xa0;
 Please submit your application here:  https://recruitment.ieseg.fr/jobs/1426114-assistant-or-associate-professor-position-in-business-ethics-business-and-society?promotion=303904-trackable-share-link-aom &#xa0;
 ABOUT ALL THREE POSITIONS
 Applicants should be completely  fluent in English  as nearly all courses at IESEG are taught in this language. Although not required (the   School   provides   French courses to faculty members), working knowledge of  French is considered an asset  for these positions. Ability (and inclination) to interact with French/local companies and partners is indeed also valued.
 Applicants should embody the  values  of the school and be  team players . Collegiality is an important part of the department/school culture.
 Applicants for a professor position should hold a PhD (or be close to obtaining it). Applicants for the position of Assistant Professor are expected to have the potential to secure publications in top-tier refereed journals in the near future. For an appointment at the Associate level applicants are required to have (a) extensive higher education teaching experience; (b) a strong publication record in top-tier refereed journals, including a solid pipeline of work and evidence of research impact; (c) good networks in academia and professional circles at French and/or international levels; and (d) grant application ability.
 APPLICATION PROCEDURE
 Please make sure to apply for the position which is in line with your expertise.&#xa0;
 When applying, please upload a single pdf file merging the following documents: (1)&#xa0;a cover letter indicating location preference (i.e. Lille or Paris campus), (2)&#xa0;a curriculum vitae (mentioning the names, affiliations, and email addresses of three referees), (3) a research statement, (4)&#xa0;a teaching statement, (5) teaching evaluations for the past years, and (6) a working paper.
 Two recommendation letters should be sent separately by the referees to:
 Dr. Fran&#xe7;ois Maon  Head of the Management &#38; Society Department
 Email:  permanentfaculty.recruitment@ieseg.fr
 THE CLOSING DATE FOR APPLICATIONS IS DECEMBER 9, 2021. AFTER THIS DEADLINE, APPLICATIONS WILL BE REVIEWED TO CONTACT SHORTLISTED CANDIDATES AND ORGANIZE INTERVIEWS IN JANUARY-MARCH 2022.</description>
								<pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 03:53:05 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

							<item>

									<link>https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15743444/clinical-assistant-associate-professor-strategic-management</link>

								<title>Clinical Assistant/Associate Professor Strategic Management | William &#38; Mary</title>
								<guid isPermaLink="true">https://jobs.aom.org/jobs/rss/15743444/clinical-assistant-associate-professor-strategic-management</guid>
								<description>Williamsburg, Virginia,  &#xa0;The Raymond A. Mason School of Business at is seeking to fill one Strategic Management teaching position. This is a full-time, continuing, non-tenure eligible (NTE) position. An earned graduate degree in Strategic Management or related field is required.&#xa0; The position requires a teaching load of 21 credits (with a possibility of a 3 credit reduction to support research), begins in August 2022, and is contingent on funding.
 Primary responsibilities of this position are teaching and service. The successful candidate should be willing and able to teach courses in multiple areas, as well as teach and develop online courses, with a primary focus on Strategic Management at the undergraduate and graduate levels. Strategic Management is currently offered as a required course for the BBA (undergraduate), Full-Time MBA, Executive MBA, Part-Time MBA, and Online MBA programs. It is considered the capstone course for most of these programs. This position is not research focused but we welcome clinical colleagues who are conducting high quality research, and we are prepared to support the continuation of productive research programs.&#xa0;&#xa0; Prior teaching experience is required and candidates with a proven record of excellent teaching will be given preference in the selection process.&#xa0;An earned graduate degree in business or a related field is required.&#xa0; Prior teaching experience is required and candidates with a proven record of excellent teaching will be given preference in the selection process. Demonstrated commitment to inclusive teaching is required. An earned doctorate degree in Strategic Management or a related field is desired. Industry experience in Strategic Management, while not required, is desirable. Preference will be given to those willing and able to teach residentially and in online modalities.
 William &#38; Mary is a premier liberal arts university, chartered in 1693, and has long been considered one of the top academic institutions in the country and a &#8220;Public Ivy.&#8221; The graduate business school has been recognized as a &#8220;Top-50&#8221; school by Business Week, the Financial Times, and the Wall Street Journal. The undergraduate program is currently ranked #15 in the Poets &#38; Quants Undergraduate Business Program Ranking. The Mason School faculty has also been highly ranked by both Bloomberg Business Week and the Princeton Review where Mason faculty rank # 3 nationally. The University is situated in historic Williamsburg, Virginia and is within an hour drive of Richmond, Norfolk, and Virginia Beach. Washington DC is within a three-hour drive. The Hampton Roads area has consistently ranked among the best places to live in the country on the dimensions of quality of life, affordability, and climate. More information about the school can be found online at&#xa0; http://mason.wm.edu/ . Required: An earned graduate degree in business or a related field is required. Prior teaching experience is required and candidates with a proven record of excellent teaching will be given preference in the selection process. Demonstrated commitment to inclusive teaching is required.
 Preferred: An earned doctorate degree in Strategic Management or a related field is desired. Industry experience in Strategic Management, while not required, is desirable. Preference will be given to those willing and able to teach residentially and in online modalities.</description>
								<pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 15:05:04 -0500</pubDate>
							</item>

					</channel>
				</rss>
